Dougal,
settle down now, please.
It won't be long.
Next.
British?
Yes.
First trip to New York?
Anything edible in there?
No.
Livestock?
Must get that fixed.
No.
Let me take a look.
Welcome to New York.
Thank you.
Next.
And it was like a... Like a wind.
Or like a... Like a ghost.
But dark.
And I saw its eyes.
Shining white eyes.
A dark wind, with eyes?
It's like a dark mass.
And it dove down there.
Down underground.
Someone ought to do something about it.
It's everywhere, this thing.
It's out of control.
Hey,
you get anything?
Dark wind. Blah, blah.
Some sorta atmospheric hooey.
Or electrical.
Hey, you thirsty?
No. I'm on the wagon.
Promised Martha I'd lay off.
It's atmospheric.
Out of the way, folks.
Coming through!
This great city sparkles
with the jewels of man's inventions.
Movie theaters, automobiles,
the wireless, electric lights,
all dazzle and bewitch us.
I'm so sorry.
But where there is light,
there is shadow, friend.
Something is stalking our city,
wreaking destruction and then
disappearing without a trace!
Listen to me.
We have to fight.
Join us, the Second Salemers, in our fight.
Excuse me doll, just trying to get to the bank.
You hear me?
We have to fight together,
Excuse me.
For the sake of our...
Hey! Watch it!
So sorry. My case.
No harm done.
Excuse me.
You!
Friend.
What drew you to our meeting today?
I was just passing.
Are you a seeker?
A seeker after truth?
I'm more of a chaser, really.
Hear my words.
And heed my warning.
And laugh if you dare.
Witches live among us.
We have to fight together
for the sake of our children.
For the sake of tomorrow.
What do you say to that, friend?
Excuse me.
Can I help you, sir?
No, I was just... I was just waiting.
Hi.
What brings you here?
Same as you.
You're here to get a loan
to open up a bakery?
Yes.
What are the odds of that?
Well, may the best man win, I guess.
Excuse me.
Hey! Hey, mister!
Hey, mister.
Hey, fella.
Mr. Kowalski,
Mr. Bingley will see you now.
Okay.
You're currently working,
in a canning factory.
That's the best I can do.
I only got back in...
24.
Got back?
From Europe, sir.
Yeah. I was part
of the expeditionary forces there.
All right.
Mr. Kowalski...
You gotta try the paczkis, okay?
It's my grandmother's recipe.
The orange zest just...
Mr. Kowalski.
What do you propose
to offer the bank as collateral?
Collateral?
Collateral.
There are machines now
that can produce hundreds
of donuts an hour.
I know. I know. But they're nothing
like what I can do. You...
The bank must be protected, Mr. Kowalski.
Good day to you.
Hey! Mr. English Guy!
I think your egg is hatching.
What just happened?
But, excuse me?
I was over there. Came over...
I was over there.
In you hop.
Hello?
No.
Everyone settle down.
Stay. Dougal, don't make me come in there.
Don't make me come down there.
Absolutely not.
Alohomora.
So you're gonna steal the money?
Petrificus Totalus.
Mr. Bingley!
Kowalski.
Really?
No. Don't play that.
Look.
Oh, no.
No, no, no. Don't...
Don't shoot.
Don't shoot!
Right. For the last time,
you pilfering pest,
paws off what doesn't belong to you.
Awfully sorry about that.
What the hell was that?
Nothing that need concern you.
Now, unfortunately,
you have seen far too much.
If you wouldn't mind,
if you just stand there,
this'll be over in a jiffy.
Sure. Yeah.
Sorry.
Bugger.
Who are you?
I'm sorry.
Newt Scamander. And you are?
What's that thing in your case?
That's my Niffler.
Say, you've got something on your...
Why in the name of Deliverance Dane
did you let that thing loose?
I didn't mean to.
He's incorrigible, you see.
Anything shiny, he's all over...
You didn't mean to?
No.
You could not have chosen
a worse time to let that creature loose.
We're in the middle of a situation here.
I'm taking you in.
Taking me in where?
Magical Congress of
the United States of America.
So you work for MACUSA.
What are you, some kind of investigator?
At least tell me
you took care of the No-Maj.
The what?
The No-Maj.
No-Magic. The non-wizard!
Sorry, we call them Muggles.
You wiped his memory, right?
The No-Maj with the case?
That's a Section 3-A, Mr. Scamander.
I'm taking you in.
Come on.
Sorry, but I do have things to do, actually.
Well...
You'll have to rearrange them.
What are you doin' in New York anyway?
I came to buy a birthday present.
Couldn't you have done that in London?
No, there's only one breeder of
Appaloosa Puffskeins in the world,
and he lives in New York. So, no.
I got a Section 3-A.
Hey.
By the way, we don't allow the breeding
of magical creatures in New York.
We closed that guy down a year ago.
Hey, Goldstein.
Hey, Red.
Major Investigation Department.
I thought you was...
I got a Section 3-A.
The International Confederation
is threatening to send a delegation.
They think this is related
to Grindelwald's attacks in Europe.
I was there.
This is a beast.
No human could do what this thing
is capable of, Madam President.
Whatever it is, one thing is clear.
It must be stopped.
It's terrorizing No-Majs.
And when No-Majs are afraid, they attack.
This could mean exposure.
It could mean war.
I made your position here
quite clear, Ms. Goldstein.
Yes, Madam President. But I...
You're no longer an Auror.
No.
Madam President, but...
Goldstein.
There's been a minor...
This office is currently concerned
with very major incidents. Get out.
Yes, ma'am.
So you got your wand permit?
All foreigners have to have them in New York.
I made a postal application weeks ago.
Scamander...
And you were just in Equatorial Guinea?
And I've just completed a year in the fields.
I'm writing a book about magical creatures.
Like an extermination guide?
No, a guide to help people understand
why we should be protecting
these creatures instead of killing them.
Goldstein?
Where is she?
Where is she? Goldstein?
Goldstein?
Did you just butt in
on the investigative team again?
Where have you been?
What?
Where'd she pick you up?
Me?
Have you been tracking
them Second Salemers again?
Of course not, sir.
Afternoon, Mr. Graves, sir.
Afternoon, Abernathy.
Mr. Graves, sir, this is Mr. Scamander.
He has a crazy creature in that case,
and it got out
and caused mayhem in a bank.
Let's see the little guy.
Tina.
I'm sorry, Grandma.
What the...
♪ My momma, your momma ♪
♪ Gonna catch a witch ♪
♪ Flying on a switch ♪
♪ My momma, your momma ♪
♪ Witches never cry ♪
♪ Witches gonna die ♪
♪ Witch number one, ♪
♪ drown in the river ♪
♪ Witch number two, ♪
got a noose to give her ♪
♪ Witch number three, ♪
♪ gonna watch her burn ♪
♪ Witch number four, ♪
♪ flogging take a turn ♪
Collect your leaflets
before you get food, children.
Is it a witch's mark, ma'am?
No.
He's okay.
I can't believe you didn't Obliviate that man.
If there's an inquiry, I'm finished.
Why would you be finished?
I'm the one that's...
I'm not supposed
to go near the Second Salemers.
What was that?
Moth, I think.
Big moth.
Hey! Hey! Quiet down!
I'm trying to get a statement.
I'm telling you, it's a gas explosion again.
I ain't taking the kids back up there
until it's safe.
Hey, sorry, ma'am.
There ain't no smell of gas.
It weren't gas, officer. I seen it.
It was a gigantic, huge hippopoto...
Gas.
Gas. It was gas!
Mr. Scamander!
It was open?
Just a smidge.
That crazy Niffler thing's on the loose again?
Might be.
Then look for it.
Look!
His neck's bleeding.
He's hurt.
Wake up! Mr. No-Maj.
Mercy Lewis, what is that?
It's nothing to worry about.
That is...
a Murtlap.
What else have you got in there?
You?
Hello.
Easy, Mr...
Kowalski. Jacob.
You can't Obliviate him.
We need him as a witness.
I'm so sorry. You've just yelled at me the length
of New York for not doing it in the first place.
He's hurt! He looks ill.
He'll be fine.
Murtlap bites aren't serious.
Yeah, I admit that is a slightly more
severe reaction than I've seen.
But if it was really serious, he'd have...
What?
Well, the first symptom
would be flames out of his anus.
He doesn't seem to...
This is balled up!
It'll last 48 hours at the most.
I can keep him, if you want me to.
Keep him?
We don't keep them.
Mr. Scamander, do you know anything
about the wizarding community in America?
I do know a few things, actually.
I know that you have rather backwards laws
about relations with Non-Magic people.
That you're not meant to befriend them.
That you can't marry them,
which seems mildly absurd to me.
Who's gonna marry him?
You're both coming with me.
I don't see why I need to come with you.
Help me.
I'm dreaming, right?
Yeah.
Please.
I'm tired.
I never went to the bank.
This is all just some big nightmare, right?
For the both of us, Mr. Kowalski.
Hey, you all right there?
And so this is the newsroom.
Let's go.
Hey, how are you?
Make way for the Barebones.
Now, they're...
just putting the papers to bed, as they say.
Mr. Shaw. Sir. He's with the Senator.
Never mind that, Barker.
I wanna see my father.
I'm so sorry, Mr. Shaw,
but your son insisted.
Father, you're gonna wanna hear this.
I've got something huge.
Your brother and I are busy here, Langdon.
Working on his election campaign.
We don't have time for this.
This is Mary Lou Barebone
from the New Salem Preservation Society.
And she's got a big story for you.
Oh, she has, has she?
There's strange things
going on all over the city.
The people behind this,
they are not like you and me.
This is witchcraft. Don't you see?
Langdon.
She doesn't want any money.
Then either her story is worthless,
or she's lying about the cost.
Nobody gives away anything
valuable for free, Langdon.
You're right, Mr. Shaw.
What we desire is infinitely
more valuable than money.
It's your influence.
Millions of people read your newspapers,
and they need to be made aware
about this danger.
The crazy disturbances in the subway.
Just look at the pictures.
I'd like you and your friends to leave.
No. Look, you're missing a trick here.
Just look at the evidence!
Really?
Langdon.
Listen to Father and just go.
And...
Take the freaks with you.
This is Father's office, not yours.
And I'm sick of this.
Every time I walk in here...
Okay. That's it!
Thank you.
We hope you'll reconsider, Mr. Shaw.
We're not difficult to find.
Until then...
we thank you for your time.
Hey, boy!
You dropped something.
Here you go, freak.
Why don't you put that in the trash
where you all belong?
Take a right here.
Okay.
Before we go in...
I'm not supposed to have men
on the premises.
In that case, Mr. Kowalski and I can
easily seek other accommodations.
No, you don't.
Watch your step.
That you, Tina?
Yes, Mrs. Esposito.
Are you alone?
I'm always alone, Mrs. Esposito.
Teenie,
you brought men home.
Gentlemen, this is my sister.
Wanna put something on, Queenie?
Oh, sure.
So, who are they?
That's Mr. Scamander.
He's committed a serious infraction
of the National Statute of Secrecy.
He's a criminal?
And that's Mr. Kowalski. He's a No-Maj.
A No-Maj?
Teen, what are you up to?
He's sick. It's a long story.
Mr. Scamander has lost something
I'm going to help him find.
You need to sit down, honey.
He hasn't eaten anything all day.
And...
Oh, that's rough.
He didn't get the money
he wanted for his bakery.
You bake, honey?
I love to cook.
You're a Legilimens?
Yeah.
But I always have trouble with your kind.
Brits.
It's the accent.
You know how to read minds?
Oh, don't worry, honey.
Most guys think what you was thinking
first time they see me.
Now, you need food.
Hot dog? Again?
Don't read my mind.
Not a very wholesome lunch.
Hey, Mr. Scamander.
You prefer pie or strudel?
I really don't have a preference.
You prefer strudel, huh, honey?
Strudel it is.
Well, sit down, Mr. Scamander.
We're not gonna poison you.
You're upset.
It's your mother again.
Somebody said something.
What did they say? Tell me.
Do you think I'm a freak?
No. I think you're a very special young man,
or I wouldn't have asked you
to help me, now would I?
Have you any news?
I'm still looking.
Mr. Graves, if I knew
whether it was a girl or a boy...
My vision showed
only the child's immense power.
He or she is no older than 10.
I saw this child
in close proximity to your mother.
She I saw so plainly.
That could be any one of hundreds...
There's something else.
Something I haven't told you.
I saw you beside me in New York.
You're the one who gains this child's trust.
You are the key. I saw this.
You want to join the wizarding world.
I want those things too, Credence.
I want them for you.
So find the child.
Find the child and we'll all be free.
The job ain't that glamorous.
I mean, I spend most days making coffee.
Unjinxing the john.
Tina's the career girl.
Nah, we're orphans.
Ma and Pa died of Dragon Pox
when we were kids.
You're sweet.
But we got each other.
Could you stop
reading my mind for a second?
Don't get me wrong, I love it.
This meal, it's insanely good.
And this is what I do, I'm a cook.
And this is like the greatest meal
I have ever had in my life.
You slay me.
I ain't never really talked to a No-Maj before.
Really?
I am not flirting.
I'm just saying, don't go getting attached.
He's gonna have to be Obliviated.
It's nothing personal.
Oh, hey, you okay, honey?
So, Ms. Goldstein, I think Mr. Kowalski
could do with an early night.
Besides, you and I will need to be up early
tomorrow morning to find my Niffler, so...
What's a Niffler?
Don't ask.
Hey, you guys can bunk in here.
I thought you might like a hot drink.
Hey. Mr. Scamander, look, cocoa.
Toilet's down the hall to the right.
Thanks.
Very much.
Come on.
For the love...
Will you sit down?
Good idea.
That's definitely the Murtlap.
You must be particularly susceptible.
See, you're a Muggle,
so our physiologies are subtly different.
Stay still.
That should stop the sweating.
And one of those should sort the twitch.
Here, take that.
Come on.
Whatcha got there?
This, the locals call Swooping Evil.
Not the friendliest of names.
It's quite an agile fella.
I've been studying him, and I'm pretty sure
that his venom could be quite useful
if properly diluted.
Just to remove bad memories, you know?
Probably shouldn't let him
loose in here, though.
Come on.
Come on. Down you come.
Thank Paracelsus.
If you'd have got out,
that could've been quite catastrophic.
So he's the real reason I came to America.
To bring Frank home.
Wait. No, sorry. Stay there.
He's a wee bit sensitive to strangers.
Here you are. Here you are.
He was trafficked, you see.
I found him in Egypt.
He was all chained up.
Couldn't leave him there.
I had to bring him back.
I'm gonna put you back
where you belong, aren't I, Frank?
To the wilds of Arizona.
All right, here they come.
Here who comes?
Graphorns.
Hey!
You're all right.
Hello.
So they're the last
breeding pair in existence.
So if I hadn't managed to rescue them,
that could've been
the end of Graphorns forever.
All right.
What, you rescue these creatures?
Yes, that's right.
Rescue, nurture and protect them.
And I'm gently trying to educate
my fellow wizards about them.
Come on.
Titus, Finn.
Poppy, Marlow, Tom.
He had a cold.
He needed some body warmth.
All right, on you hop.
He has some attachment issues.
Now, come on, Pickett.
Pickett.
No, they're not gonna bully you,
now come on.
Pickett.
All right.
And that is exactly why
they accuse me of favoritism.
Oh, no, Dougal's gone.
All right, I'm coming. I'm coming.
Mum's here. Mum's here.
Oh, hello.
Let me take a look at you.
I know these guys.
Your Occamy.
What do you mean, my Occamy?
Yes.
Do you want to...
Yeah, sure.
Okay.
Hey.
Oh, sorry, no, don't pet him.
They... learn to defend themselves early.
See, their shells are made of silver,
so they're incredibly valuable.
Okay.
Their nests tend to get
ransacked by hunters.
Thank you.
Mr. Scamander?
Oh, call me Newt.
Newt. I don't think I'm dreaming.
What gave it away?
I ain't got the brains to make this up.
Would you mind throwing some of those
pellets in with the Mooncalfs over there?
Yeah, sure.
Just over there's...
Bugger.
Niffler's gone.
Course he has, little bugger.
Any chance to get his hands
on something shiny.
What did you do today, Jacob?
I was inside a suitcase.
Hey.
Oh, hello, fellas.
All right. All right.
Take it easy. Take it easy.
Cutie.
There it is.
Step back.
What's the matter with this?
I said, step away.
What the hell is this thing?
It's an Obscurus.
I need to get going.
Find everyone who's escaped,
before they get hurt.
Before they get hurt?
Yes, Mr. Kowalski.
So they're currently in alien terrain
surrounded by millions of the most
vicious creatures on the planet.
Humans.
So where would you say
that a medium-sized creature
who likes broad open plains,
trees, sort of waterholes,
that sort of thing.
Where might she go?
In New York City?
Yes.
Plains?
Central Park.
And where is that exactly?
Where is Central Park?
Well, look...
I would come and show you,
but don't you think it's kind
of a double-cross?
The girls take us in,
they make us hot cocoa...
Now you do realize that once they see
that you stopped sweating,
they will Obliviate you in a heartbeat?
What's "Bliviate" mean?
It'll be like you wake up
and all memory of magic gone.
I won't remember any of this?
No.
All right, yeah, okay. I'll help you.
Come on, then.
Credence, where have you been?
I was looking for a place
for tomorrow's meeting.
There's a corner on 32nd Street that could...
I'm sorry, Ma.
I didn't realize it was so late.
I was watching you at dinner.
Yeah.
People like you, don't they, Mr. Kowalski?
Well, I'm sure people like you, too?
Not really, no. I annoy people.
Why did you decide to be a baker?
Well...
Because I'm dying,
in that canning factory.
Everyone there's dying.
It just crushes the life out of you.
Do you like canned food?
No.
Yeah, me neither.
That's why I wanna make pastries.
You know, it makes people happy.
We're going this way.
So did you get your loan?
No.
I ain't got no collateral.
Stayed in the army too long, apparently.
I don't know.
You fought in the war?
Of course I fought in the war.
Everyone fought in the war.
You didn't fight in the war?
I worked mostly with dragons.
Ukrainian Ironbellies.
Eastern Front.
Fenestra.
Accio.
All right. Happy?
One down, two to go.
They went that way, officer.
Hands up.
What the hell is that?
Lion.
You know,
New York is considerably
more interesting than I'd expected.
Put this on.
But why would I have to wear
something like this?
Because your skull is susceptible
to breakage under immense force.
But we made them cocoa.
All right.
Here, you just, pop this on.
Okay.
Now there's absolutely
nothing for you to worry about.
Tell me, has anyone ever believed you
when you told them not to worry?
Well, my philosophy is that
worrying means you suffer twice.
She's in season.
She needs to mate.
Erumpent musk. She's mad for it.
Good girl.
Come on.
Into the case.
Get!
Oh, no.
Reparo.
Merlin's beard!
Tree!
They're exactly the same.
Same thing.
Newt!
No, don't.
I'm so sorry.
Good show, Mr. Kowalski.
Call me Jacob.
Well...
Two down, one to go.
In you hop.
Ladies and gentlemen...
Tonight's keynote speaker
needs no introduction from me.
He's been mentioned as a future president.
And if you don't believe me,
just read his daddy's newspapers.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I give you the senator for New York...
Henry Shaw.
Thank you.
And it's true,
we have made some progress.
But there is no reward for idleness.
So just as the odious saloons,
have been banished.
So now the pool halls,
and these private parlors...
What is that?
No! No!
Witches.
Our American friends
have permitted a breach
of the Statute of Secrecy that
threatens to expose us all.
I will not be lectured by the man
who let Gellert Grindelwald
slip through his fingers.
Madam President, I'm sorry to interrupt,
but this is critical...
You better have an excellent excuse,
for this intrusion, Ms. Goldstein.
Yes. I do.
Ma'am,
yesterday a wizard entered
New York with a case,
this case full of magical creatures.
And unfortunately, some have escaped.
He arrived yesterday?
You've known for 24 hours,
that an unregistered wizard set
magical beasts loose in New York and you see
fit to tell us only when a man has been killed?
Who's been killed?
Where is this man?
Scamander?
Hello, Minister.
Theseus Scamander?
The war hero?
No. This is his little brother.
And what are you doing in New York?
I came to buy an Appaloosa Puffskein, sir.
Right.
What are you really doing here?
Goldstein,
who is this?
This is Jacob Kowalski, Madam President.
He's a No-Maj who got bitten
by one of Mr. Scamander's creatures.
No-Maj? Obliviate him.
Obliviate him.
Merlin's beard.
You know which of your creatures
was responsible, Mr. Scamander?
No creature did this.
Don't pretend.
You must know what that was.
Look at the marks.
That was an Obscurus.
You go too far, Mr. Scamander.
There is no Obscurial in America.
Impound that case, Graves.
Wait, no. Give that back.
Arrest them.
Don't hurt those creatures.
Please. You don't understand.
Nothing in there's dangerous.
Nothing.
We'll be the judges of that.
Take them to the cells.
Don't hurt those creatures.
Nothing in there is dangerous.
Please don't hurt my creatures.
They aren't dangerous!
Please! They're not dangerous!
They're not dangerous!
I'm so sorry about your creatures,
Mr. Scamander.
I truly am.
Can someone please tell me what this
Obscurial, Obscurius thing is, please?
There hasn't been one for centuries.
I met one in Sudan three months ago.
There used to be more of them,
but they still exist.
It was before wizards went underground,
when we were still
being hunted by Muggles.
Young wizards and witches
sometimes tried to suppress their magic
to avoid persecution.
So, instead of learning to harness
or to control their powers,
they developed
what was called an Obscurus.
It's an unstable, uncontrollable dark
force that busts out and attacks.
And then vanishes.
Obscurials can't survive long, can they?
There's no documented case of an Obscurial
surviving past the age of 10.
The one I met in Africa was 8 when she...
She was 8 when she died.
What are you telling me here?
That Senator Shaw was killed by a kid?
♪ My momma, your momma ♪
♪ Flying on a switch ♪
♪ Witches never cry ♪
♪ My momma, your momma ♪
♪ Witches gonna die ♪
♪ Witch number one, drown in the river ♪
♪ Witch number two, got a noose... ♪
Hand out your leaflets.
I'll know if you dump them.
Tell me if you see anything suspicious.
It was good to make
your acquaintance, Jacob.
And I hope you get your bakery.
You're an interesting man, Mr. Scamander.
Mr. Graves.
You were thrown out of Hogwarts
for endangering human life.
That was an accident.
With a beast.
Yet one of your teachers argued
strongly against your expulsion. Now...
what makes Albus Dumbledore,
so fond of you?
I really couldn't say.
So setting a pack
of dangerous creatures loose here was...
just another accident. Is that right?
Why would I do it deliberately?
To expose wizardkind.
To provoke war between
the magical and non-magical worlds.
Mass slaughter for the greater good, you mean?
Yes.
Quite.
I'm not one of Grindelwald's fanatics,
Mr. Graves.
I wonder what you can tell me about this...
Mr. Scamander.
It's an Obscurus.
But it's not what you think.
So I managed to separate it from the
Sudanese girl as I tried to save her.
So I wanted to take it home to study it.
But it cannot survive outside that.
It could not hurt anyone, Tina.
So it's useless without the host?
Useless?
That is a parasitical,
magical force that killed a child.
What on earth would you use it for?
You fool nobody, Mr. Scamander.
You brought this Obscurus
into the City of New York
in the hope of causing mass disruption,
breaking the Statute of Secrecy
and revealing the magical world.
You know that can't hurt anyone.
You know that.
You are therefore guilty
of a treasonous betrayal
of your fellow wizards
and are sentenced to death.
Miss Goldstein, who has aided and abetted you.
No, she's done nothing of the kind.
She receives the same sentence.
Just do it immediately.
I will inform President Picquery myself.
Tina.
Please.
Don't do this, Bernadette. Please.
It don't hurt.
Tina.
Momma?
Come on, pumpkin. Time for bed.
Are you ready?
Don't that look good?
You wanna get in?
Hey, Sam.
Hey, Queenie.
They need you downstairs.
I'll Obliviate this guy.
You ain't qualified.
Hey, Sam.
Does Cecily know you been seeing Ruby?
How did you...
Let me Obliviate this guy,
and she'll never hear about it from me.
What are you doing?
Teen's in trouble.
I'm trying to listen.
Jacob, where's Newt's case?
I think that guy Graves took it.
Okay. Come on.
What, you're not gonna Obliviate me?
Of course not. You're one of us now.
Tina.
It's okay.
Alohomora.
Aberto.
He would know
some fancy spell to lock his office.
Okay, let's get the good stuff outta you.
Witch!
Mr. Scamander!
Don't panic.
What do you suggest I do instead?
Jump.
Are you crazy?
Jump on him.
Tina, listen to me.
I'll catch you.
Tina.
I've got you, Tina.
Go!
Come on.
Leave his brains. Come on. Come on!
What is that thing?
Swooping Evil.
Well, I love it.
Get in.
Queenie!
Where you going?
I...
I'm sick, Mr. Abernathy.
Again?
Whatcha got there?
Ladies' things.
You wanna take a look? I don't mind.
Good gravy. No. I...
I...
You get well now.
Thanks.
Credence, have you found the child?
I can't.
Show me.
My boy, the sooner we find this child,
the sooner you can put that pain
in the past where it belongs.
I want you to have this, Credence.
I would trust very few with it.
Very few.
But you...
You're different.
And when you find the child,
you touch this symbol,
and I will know and I will come to you.
Do this, and you will be honored,
among wizards forever.
The child is dying, Credence.
Time is running out.
Your grandfather kept pigeons?
Mine bred owls.
I used to love feeding them.
Graves always insisted
the disturbances were caused by a beast.
We need to catch all your creatures
so he can't
keep using them as a scapegoat.
There's only one still missing.
Dougal, my Demiguise.
Dougal?
Slight problem is that...
he's invisible.
Invisible?
Yes.
Most of the time. He does...
How do you catch something...
With immense difficulty.
Gnarlak.
Excuse me?
He was an informant of mine
when I was an Auror.
He used to trade
in magical creatures on the side.
He wouldn't happen to have an interest
in paw prints, would he?
He's interested in anything he can sell.
How's a guy get a drink in this joint?
What? Ain't you ever seen
a house-elf before?
No. No, of course I have...
I love house-elves.
My uncle is a house-elf.
Yeah.
Six shots of Gigglewater
and a Lobe-Blaster, please.
Are all No-Majs like you?
No.
I'm the only one like me.
I've arrested half of the people in here.
You can tell me to mind my business but,
I saw something,
in that death potion back there.
I saw you hugging that Second Salem boy.
His name's Credence.
His mother beats him.
She beats all those kids she's adopted,
but she seems to hate him the most.
She was the No-Maj you attacked?
That's how I lost my job.
I went for her in front of a meeting
of her crazy followers.
They all had to be Obliviated.
It was a big scandal.
It's him.
So...
You're the guy with the case full of monsters?
News travels fast.
I was hoping you'd be able to tell me
if there've been any sightings.
Tracks, that sort of thing.
You got a pretty big price
on your head, Mr. Scamander.
Why should I help you...
instead of turning you in?
I take it I'll have to make it
worth your while.
Let's consider it a cover charge.
MACUSA's offering more than that.
Lunascope?
I got five.
Frozen Ashwinder egg.
Oh, you see, now we're...
Wait a minute.
That's a Bow...
That's a Bowtruckle.
Right?
No.
Oh, come on.
They pick locks, am I right?
You're not having him.
Well...
Good luck getting back alive,
Mr. Scamander,
what with the whole of MACUSA
on your back.
All right.
Pickett.
Something invisible's been
wreaking havoc around 5th Avenue.
You may want to check out
Macy's Department Store.
Might have what you're looking for.
Dougal.
One last thing.
There's a Mr. Graves who works at MACUSA.
I was wondering what you knew
of his background.
You ask a lot of questions, Mr. Scamander.
That can get you killed.
MACUSA are coming.
You tipped them off?
Sorry, Mr. Gnarlak.
He reminds me of my foreman.
Whatcha doing, Credence?
Where'd you get this?
Give it back, Credence.
It's just a toy.
What is this?
Take it off.
Ma...
I am not your ma.
Your mother,
was a wicked,
unnatural woman.
It was mine.
Modesty.
What is this?
Demiguise are fundamentally peaceful,
but they can give a nasty nip if provoked.
You two,
head that way.
And try very hard not to be predictable.
Was that the Demiguise?
No.
But I think it might be the reason
that the Demiguise is here.
Its sight operates on probability,
so it can foresee
the most likely immediate future.
What's it doing?
He's babysitting.
What did you just say?
This is my fault.
I thought I had them all,
but I must have miscounted.
It was babysitting that?
Occamies are choranaptyxic.
So they grow to fill available space.
Mummy's here.
We need an insect!
Any kind of insect and a teapot.
Find a teapot!
No!
I got it! I'll get it!
Teapot!
Roach in teapot.
Choranaptyxic.
They also shrink to fit the available space.
Tell me the truth.
Was that everything
that came out of the case?
That's everything.
And that's the truth.
Here she comes.
You happy to be home? Yeah.
Bet you're exhausted, buddy. Come on.
Just place him in the middle there.
There you go. That's right.
Right.
I think we need to talk.
I wouldn't have let him keep you, Pickett.
Think I would rather chop off my hand
than get rid of you
after everything that you've done for me.
Now, come on.
Think we've talked about
the sulking before, haven't we?
Pickett?
Come on, give me a smile.
Pickett, give me a...
All right.
Now that is beneath you.
Hey, Newt.
Who is she?
Oh, that's no one.
Leta Lestrange.
I've heard of that family.
Aren't they kind of, you know...
Please don't read my mind.
Sorry, I asked you not to.
I know. I'm sorry.
I can't help it.
People are easiest to read
when they're hurting.
I'm not hurting.
Anyway, it was a long time ago.
That was a real close friendship
you had at school.
Neither of us really fitted in at school.
So, we became quite...
You became real close?
For years.
She was a taker.
You need a giver.
What are you two talking about?
Nothing.
School.
Did...
Did you say school?
Is there a school?
A wizardry school here in...
America?
Of course. Ilvermorny.
It's only the best wizard school
in the whole world.
I think you'll find that the best
wizarding school in the world is Hogwarts.
Hogwash.
Danger.
He senses danger.
The Obscurial was here.
Where did she go?
Help me.
Didn't you tell me you had another sister?
Please, help me.
Where's your other sister, Credence?
I need help.
The little one. Where did she go?
Please, just help me.
Your sister's in grave danger.
We need to find her.
What is this place?
Ma adopted Modesty out of here.
From a family of 12.
She misses her brothers and sisters.
She still talks about them.
Where is she?
I don't know.
You're a Squib, Credence.
I could smell it off you the minute I met you.
What?
You have magical ancestry but no power.
But you said you could teach me.
You're unteachable.
Your mother's dead.
That's your reward.
I'm done with you.
Modesty?
Modesty.
There's no need to be afraid.
I'm here with your brother, Credence.
Out you come now.
Credence.
I owe you an apology.
I trusted you.
I thought you were my friend.
I thought you were different.
You can control it.
Credence.
I don't think I want to, Mr. Graves.
Is that it?
That's the Obscurial thing?
That's more powerful
than any Obscurial I've ever heard of.
If I don't come back,
look after my creatures.
Everything that you need to know
is in there.
What?
They're not killing it.
Newt!
You heard him. Look after them.
Keep hold of that, honey.
No, no, no, no.
I can't take you.
Please, let go of me, Jacob.
You're the one that said I was one of yous.
Right?
It's too dangerous.
To survive so long
with this inside you, Credence,
is a miracle.
You are a miracle.
Come with me.
Think of what we could achieve together.
Newt!
It's the Second Salem boy.
He's the Obscurial.
He's not a child.
His. His power must be so strong,
he's somehow managed to survive.
Newt.
Save him.
Mr. Graves.
Tina, you're always turning up
where you're least wanted.
Contain this.
Or we are exposed, and it'll mean war.
Credence.
Credence, I can help.
Bar the area.
Yes, sir.
I don't want anyone else down there.
Credence...
It is Credence, isn't it?
I'm here to help you, Credence.
I'm not here to hurt you.
I've met someone just like you, Credence.
A girl.
A young girl
who'd been imprisoned.
She had been locked away,
and she'd been punished for her magic.
Credence.
Can I come over to you?
Can I come over?
That thing killed my son.
I want justice.
I'll expose you
for who you are and what you've done.
Look! Take photos.
Credence...
Credence, no!
Don't do this.
Please.
Keep talking, Tina.
Keep talking to him. He'll listen to you.
He's listening.
I know what that woman did to you.
I know that you've suffered.
You need to stop this now.
Newt and I will protect you.
This man,
he's using you.
Don't listen to her, Credence.
I want you to be free.
It's all right.
That's it.
Don't!
You'll frighten him!
Wands down!
Anyone harms him, they answer to me.
Credence.
No!
You fools.
Do you realize what you've done?
The Obscurial was killed
on my orders, Mr. Graves.
Yes.
And history will surely note that,
Madam President.
What was done here tonight was not right.
He was responsible
for the death of a No-Maj.
He risked the exposure of our community.
He has broken one of our most sacred laws.
A law that has us scuttling
like rats in the gutter.
A law that demands that
we conceal our true nature.
A law that directs those under its dominion
to cower in fear, lest we risk discovery.
I ask you, Madam President,
I ask all of you...
Who does this law protect?
Us?
Or them?
I refuse to bow down any longer.
Aurors,
I'd like you to relieve Mr. Graves of his wand
and escort him back...
Accio!
Revelio.
Do you think you can hold me?
We'll do our best, Mr. Grindelwald.
Will we die just a little?
Hey.
I figured somebody ought to
keep an eye on this thing.
Thank you.
We owe you an apology, Mr. Scamander,
but the magical community is exposed.
We cannot Obliviate an entire city.
Actually,
I think we can.
I was intending to wait
until we got to Arizona.
But it seems that now
you're our only hope, Frank.
I'll miss you, too.
You know what you gotta do.
They won't remember anything.
That venom has incredibly powerful
Obliviative properties.
We owe you a great debt, Mr. Scamander.
Now,
get that case out of New York.
Yes, Madam President.
Is that No-Maj still here?
Obliviate him.
There can be no exceptions.
I'm sorry, but even one witness...
You know the law.
I'll let you say goodbye.
Hey.
This is for the best.
Yeah. I was...
I was never even supposed to be here.
I was never supposed to know...
any of this.
Everybody knows Newt only
kept me around because...
Hey,
Newt, why did you keep me around?
Because I like you.
Because you're my friend.
And I'll never forget
how you helped me, Jacob.
Hey...
I'll come with you.
We'll go somewhere. We'll go anywhere.
See,
I ain't never gonna find anyone like you.
There's loads like me.
No.
There's only one like you.
I gotta go.
Jacob...
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
It's just like waking up, right?
I'm so sorry. Sorry.
Hey!
Dear Mr. Kowalski.
You are wasted in a canning factory.
Please take these Occamy eggshells
as collateral for your bakery.
A well-wisher.
Well...
It's been...
Hasn't it?
Listen, Newt...
I wanted to thank you.
What on earth for?
Well, you know...
If you hadn't said all those nice
things to Madam Picquery about me,
I wouldn't be back
on the investigative team now.
I can't think of anyone
that I'd rather have investigating me.
Try not to need investigating for a bit.
I will.
A quiet life for me from now on.
Back to the Ministry.
Deliver my manuscript.
I'll look out for it.
Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them.
Does Leta Lestrange like to read?
Who?
The girl whose picture you carry.
I don't really know
what Leta likes these days.
'Cause people change.
Yes.
I've changed.
I think...
Maybe a little.
I'll send you a copy of my book, if I may.
I'd like that.
I'm so sorry. How would you feel if I...
I gave you your copy in person?
I'd like that.
Very much.
Where'd you get your ideas
from, Mr. Kowalski?
I don't know.
They just come.
Here you go. Don't forget this.
Enjoy.
Hey! Hendry.
Storage, all right?
Thanks, pal.
By LESAIGNEUR
Sync & corrections May 2017