August 6th.
Today my colleagues will reach the site
Where an ancient civilization may
have created a shrine to Mew
The most powerful Pokemon to
have ever existed...
Now believed to be extinct.
Giovanni is financing the expedition.
When he learned of my work
in the field of cloning,
He agreed to fund my research,
but only if...
I would try to create for him, an
enhanced living replica of Mew.
I had to agree.
All he wants is to control the most powerful
Pokemon the world has ever known.
I, of course, want something more...
Much more.
Mew.
Our team is bringing back what
we believe to be a Mew fossil.
I pray, it's authentic.
If so, I may finally have the DNA
I need to create a Pokemon powerful
enough to survive the cloning process.
Perhaps then, I can unlock the
secret to restoring life itself.
Where am I?
Who am I?
What am I?
It's just like all the other clones,
doctor. It hasn't gained consciousness.
I just don't understand it. It's
other vital signs are strong.
We're measuring brain activity...
I sense others near me.
What are those strange sounds they make?
Those are words. They're talking.
What are you?
What do you mean? I'm a girl.
A person.
A person? Am I a person?
Well, you look like a Pokemon,
but you talk.
I didn't know, a Pokemon could
talk like a person.
Pokemon? Person? What are those?
Which one am I?
Maybe it makes a difference to you
If you are a Pokemon or a person,
but not to me.
If you're in this place, I guess you
must be the same as all of us are
- What's that?
- I'm not sure.
But Mewtwo and Ambertwo seem to be
communicating with the other clones.
- But how?
- They could be using telepathy.
Soon.
Everybody here is a copy.
That's why there is a "Two"
after all of our names.
I don't understand.
They call me "Ambertwo",
But I'm still really Amber.
Please, please let my theories be true.
I must see my little girl smile...
Again.
Dear?
I reawakened her consciousness,
here, in this chamber!
I just need to keep it viable long
enough to complete the process!
Why are you doing this?
- You can't bring Amber back.
- You are wrong!
Look, she lives within this light.
Her energy is undeniable.
If my cloning theories are correct, We'll
have Amber back with us one day, soon.
"I loved our daughter, as much
as you did. But she is gone.
No one can bring her back. And
I can't go on watching you try.
I'm sorry.
Goodbye."
I'll do anything, to see you again.
So, how are they doing today?
You should be very pleased, doctor.
The Pokemon clones are in stable condition,
and the Mewtwo is getting stronger every day.
One of them is bound to survive.
It looks like all our hard
work is finally paying off.
Yes, Giovanni will be very happy,
I'm sure.
He may soon have the most
powerful Pokemon in the world.
But I'll get something
much more precious:
Knowledge, of how to recreate life.
Then, I'll use it to bring her back.
I call this my "Remember Place".
This is where I used to live.
What is that?
That's the sun.
What is it for?
It makes the whole world bright,
And it keeps us warm all day.
- That's called "wind"
- "Wind"?
The wind helps us along.
Sometimes it's soft, and
sometimes It's very strong.
And that's the sunset.
That's when the sun says:
"Goodnight, see you tomorrow"
Is that a sun?
No, that's the moon.
And the stars are the little
lights that twinkle all night,
Just so we won't
feel alone in the dark.
We're losing all readings
from Charmandertwo.
No, not again!
Bulbasaurtwo and Squirtletwo
are fading the same way!
It looks like another failure.
Where did they go?
Doctor, we're losing her too.
Amber...
What's wrong, Amber?
What's happening?
It feels like it's time to say goodbye.
Goodbye?
I feel something.
What are these?
They are tears. You're crying.
- Crying?
- My daddy used to tell me a bedtime story...
...That when Pokemon were sad, and they
cried, their tears were filled with life.
I'm so... Sad.
- I have to go.
- Why?
I don't know.
But it's allright.
Thank you for caring about me.
And don't cry, Mewtwo.
You should be happy. You're alive.
And life is wonderful.
These tears, what good are they?
Please, Amber.
Come back.
Don't go, please!
Amber!
Doctor, Mewtwo's
brainwaves are out of control!
It's getting too upset, it mustn't
remember this, administer the serum!
- Do it immediately!
- I'll try a 100 units.
10, 20, 30, 40...
...50, 60, 70, 80...
...90, 100.
- What's happening? Is it working?
It's brainwaves are going back to normal.
Everything seems okay, doctor.
Nothing is okay.
My Amber is gone forever.
Only Mewtwo survives.
I have slept for so long...
... It seems like... Forever.
But I remember something.
Someone.
"Life is wonderful."
But... Why?
Narrator: Life...
The great miracle and the great mystery.
Who am I?
Since the beginning, humans and Pokemon alike
Have searched for its meaning.
What am I?
Many strange and wondrous legends evolved
From the pursuit of life's mysteries.
Where am I?
But none is stranger than this tale
Of the most powerful Pokemon of all.
I am ready...
To be.
Where... Am I?
This-- this is not the same.
Was everything before just a dream?
Why?
Female scientist: Doctor, look at this.
Male scientist: What?
Its brain waves, they're surging!
Let's go see! She's right!
Male scientist: Let's run another scan.
Its mind is racing!
Those voices...
Male scientist: I hope we don't lose this one.
They're outside...
We can't lose this one.
Where I must be.
Oh!
[Alarm sounding]
Radio Giovanni's helicopter!
Tell him what's happened!
Male scientist: Quiet!
Let us hear its psychic powers.
Psychic powers?
For years we struggled to
successfully clone a Pokemon
To prove our theories,
But you're the first specimen to survive.
That is Mew, the rarest of all Pokemon.
From its DNA we created you-- Mewtwo.
Mewtwo?
Am I only a copy?
Nothing but Mew's shadow?
You are greater than Mew,
Improved through the power of human ingenuity.
We used the most advanced techniques
To develop your awesome psychic powers.
So, I am simply the end
result of your experiment.
What becomes of me now that
your experiment is over?
Our experiment isn't over yet.
It's just beginning.
Now the serious testing begins.
These humans, they care nothing for me.
Congratulations. We've done it.
[All talking at once]
Is the new tank ready?
No. We'll have to come up with a cage.
Congratulations. Ha ha!
Excellent. We'll start our testing
right away.
Is that my purpose?
Am I just an experiment?
A laboratory specimen?
This cannot be my destiny.
Oh!
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
We dreamed of creating the
world's strongest Pokemon...
And we succeeded.
[Helicopter]
Behold my powers.
I am the strongest Pokemon in the world.
Stronger even than Mew.
Those fools thought you
were a science experiment.
But i, I see you as a valuable partner.
Partner?
With your psychic powers and my resources,
Together we can control the world.
I do not need your help for that, human.
A wildfire destroys everything in its path.
It will be the same with your powers
Unless you learn to control them.
I can help you do that.
How?
Trust me, and I'll show you a way
To focus your powers
That will make you invincible.
Show me.
[Chuckles]
You say this armor protects my body,
Yet it suppresses my powers.
Your powers are not being suppressed.
They're being focused.
Learn to use them to accomplish your purpose.
What is that?
Patience, my friend.
Your purpose will become clear.
[Onix growls]
[Snaps]
[Roars]
So, this is my power.
[Mooing]
I am in control now.
Alakazam!
[Grunting]
Kazam!
But why am I here?
Now I fully perceive my power.
But what is my purpose?
[Footsteps]
Giovanni: To serve your master.
You were created to fight for me.
That is your purpose.
That cannot be.
You said we were partners.
We stood as equals.
You were created by humans to obey humans.
You could never be our equal.
Humans may have created me,
But they will never enslave me!
This cannot be my destiny!
Stop this now!
I was not born of Pokemon.
I was created.
And my creators have used and betrayed me.
So, I stand alone!
Aah!
Who am I?
What is my true reason for being?
I will find my own purpose...
And purge this planet of all who oppose me.
Human and Pokemon alike.
The world will heed my warning.
The reign of Mewtwo
Will soon begin.
Narrator: Today, Ash, Brock, and Misty
Are taking a short break from
their Pokemon adventures.
As always, Ash is determined
to become a Pokemon master,
And, as always, he's ready
to endure any hardship,
Bear any burden with strength, stamina,
And a will of steel.
Hungry. Need food.
Oh, Ash. You haven't done a thing all day.
I'm too weak to work, Misty.
I haven't eaten since breakfast.
Oh.
This lunch is gonna be just perfect for you, Ash.
It's my lazy-boy no-chew stew.
Toge Toge!
Pika?
Toge?
[Squeaks]
Hey! You there!
I'm lookin' for a Pokemon trainer
Named Ash from Pallet Town.
You know him?
Yeah, he's me.
Let's have a match.
Unless you're afraid to lose.
Ha! I'm afraid you're gonna lose this one.
Ash, you just said you were too weak to work.
That's right, I am too weak to work,
But a Pokemon battle isn't work.
That's progress.
At least his mouth is working.
Pikachu.
# I wanna be the very best #
# Like no one ever was #
# To catch them is my real test #
# To train them is my cause #
# Whoo whoo whoo #
# I will travel across the land #
# Searching far and wide #
# Each Pokemon to understand #
# The power that's inside #
# Inside #
# Pokemon #
# It's you and me #
# I know it's my destiny #
# Pokemon #
# Ooh, you're my best friend #
# In a world we must defend #
# Pokemon #
# A heart so true #
# Our courage will pull us through #
# You teach me, and I'll teach you #
# Pokemon #
# Gotta catch 'em #
# Gotta catch 'em all #
Great job, Bulbasaur. Ha.
You did it.
# Every challenge #
# Along the way #
# With courage I will face
# I will battle everything
# Claim my rightful place #
# Come with me, the time is right #
# There's no better team, yeah #
# Arm in arm, we'll win the fight #
# It's always been a dream #
# It's always been a dream
# Pokemon #
# It's you and me #
# I know it's my destiny #
# Pokemon #
# Ooh, you're my best friend #
# In a world we must defend #
# Pokemon #
# I'm, oh, so true #
Ha ha ha ha!
# You teach me, and I'll teach you #
# Pokemon #
# I'll teach you #
# Gotta catch 'em #
Pika...
# Gotta catch 'em all #
Chu!
Uhh!
Oh, no!
We did it!
Pika!
Well, that sure was a shocking ending.
Shocking that Ash moved so fast.
Toge!
Ha ha ha!
Pikachu.
There's another credit
On Pikachu's charge account.
We've got to grab it.
I know we got to grab some
rare Pokemon for the boss,
But it wouldn't be such a bad idea
If we grabbed a little bite to eat, would it?
We didn't come here to steal a meal.
I'd settle for a taste of that Pika-chow.
Pika. Pika. Pika.
Squirt.
[Groans] I'm starvin'.
I can cook something.
Thanks, but the last time you cooked,
You wiped out 8 of my 9 lives.
[All sigh]
Pika Pika... Chu!
[Chuckles]
[Squeaks]
Ha ha ha!
[Caws]
Master, shall I extend an invitation
To these trainers as well?
As you wish.
[Grunts]
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Ohh! Yeow!
Aah! Aah! Squirt!
Hey, watch where you're flyin'.
Huh? Somethin' for me?
Hmm...
Misty: Wow!
Greetings, Pokemon trainers.
I bear an invitation.
She's really small, but really pretty.
You have been chosen to join a select group
Of Pokemon trainers at a special gathering.
It will be hosted by my master,
The world's greatest Pokemon trainer,
At his palace on new island.
A chartered ferry
Will leave from old shore wharf
To take you to the island this afternoon.
Only trainers who present this invitation
Will be admitted.
If you decide to attend, you must reply at once.
My master awaits you.
Uh, is there a rewind button?
Should we go?
Of course we should!
I've gotta meet her!
I guess the world's number one trainer
Wants to challenge me to a match!
Pika.
Hmm? Well, we've gotta let 'em know right away.
I'm sayin' yes.
Pika?
Toge.
[Grunts]
We wanna know what's so special
About the twerp trio's special delivery!
Hey, look!
"Yes"? To what?
Mew.
[Togepi squeaks]
Pika. Pika. Pi.
Raticate!
Chill out, Raticate!
Kingler! Save your energy, will ya?
This is gonna be so cool.
P.A.: Officer Jenny,
Please report to the ferry entrance.
Officer Jenny,
To the ferry entrance, please.
Togepi's totally soaked.
I can't believe how fast the storm came up.
Aah!
Huh? What?
The ferry is canceled?
But I've got to get to new island.
Yeah, so do I.
What's the big deal?
It's only a little rain.
It's more than just rain.
The harbor manager
Thinks this could be the worst storm ever.
Listen to me.
The prophets have predicted
The return of the winds of water.
For years, I have prayed
That mankind would never witness
That deadly storm ever again.
Isn't that just a legend?
The ancient writings tell of the storm
Wiping out all but a few Pokemon.
In their sorrow, the water of their tears
Somehow restored the lives lost in the storm.
But there are no Pokemon tears today.
Just waters which no one can survive.
And that's why your ferry
To new island's been canceled.
Well, I'm going to new island anyway.
All my Pokemon are water-type.
Not fair.
We'll just swim over to that palace.
I warn you, the waves will be savage.
You will never make it.
And besides, if you tried that stunt
And your Pokemon got hurt, you'd be out of luck,
Because we had to close down the Pokemon center.
Uh, how come?
Because the nurse in charge of the center
Disappeared last month.
And if any of you see her,
please contact me at once.
That's a picture of her over there on the wall.
Mmm. She's cute. Huh.
She sure looks familiar.
Aah! Aah!
[Roars]
Aah!
Come back here!
Or I'll place you under arrest!
Dewgong-gong.
Come back! Aah!
Some trainers have no fear.
Huh?
To them, this is just one more challenge.
They follow their hearts.
That is what sets them apart
And will make them Pokemon masters.
Good luck to all of you.
The world's greatest Pokemon master
Is waiting for me.
Let's use our Pokemon to get to that island.
Pika!
Ash, our Pokemon aren't strong enough.
They can't handle giant waves like this.
Guess you're right.
Pika Pika.
[Scandinavian accent] You vant to cross maybe?
Ve take you, ja?
Ve vikings are used to big vaves.
Ve get to new island
Faster than you can say fahrvernugen.
Stroke!
Uhh!
Uhh! Uhh!
Stroke! Stroke!
Stroke!
Oh, I think I'm gonna have one.
I didn't know vikings still existed.
They mostly live in Minnesota.
Something's not right.
Are you sure this boat's safe?
Whoa! Pika!
Don't vorry. This ship von't let you down.
Ve alvays sail in da rough veather.
Don't get upset.
Tell my stomach.
Heave. Ho.
It's all right, Togepi. We're gonna be ok.
Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Pika!
Those aren't vikings!
It's Team Rocket.
I should've known there was
something fishy about them
Besides the way they smell.
Ha! Prepare for trouble.
Make it double.
Meowth: Forget the motto. We're gonna have to--
Aah! Aah! Aah!
Staryu: hyah!
Hyah!
Ash! Misty!
Uhh! Ohh!
Aah! Aah!
Have you seen Ash and Pikachu?
Not yet.
Aah! Aah!
[Gasps]
Stay together. It's our only hope.
Pika!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
[Grunting]
Uhh. Squirtle. Squirtle.
[Gasping, panting]
Huh?
Pi Pika!
Hmm? Hmm?
Hey, look!
Hmm?
[Togepi squeaks]
My master bids you welcome to new island.
Will you kindly present your invitation?
Uh... Um...
Here it is, miss.
The bearers of this invitation
May be admitted to new island.
I knew I recognized that face.
What?
Brock: Aren't you the nurse
Who's missing from the treatment center?
You do look just like her.
I fear you are mistaken.
I have always dwelt on this island
And have always been in the service of my master.
Please, come this way.
My master awaits your arrival.
Uhh! Uhh! Uhh! Uhh!
Mew.
Mew!
Mew. Mew.
Uhh.
Hmm...
Huh?
[Doors creak open]
Now that you are here, all trainers
Worthy of an audience with my master are present.
Huh? Huh?
Wigglytuff: Wiggly.
Wiggly.
There's only 3 of 'em.
Aren't we going to wait for the others?
Only the trainers capable of braving the storm
Have proven themselves
worthy in my master's eyes.
Do you mean that storm was some kind of test?
Please release your Pokemon from their Pokeballs
And join the others.
It will not be long
Before my master's intentions are clear.
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Locked out. Now we'll never know
What kind of party we're missing.
Then we'll just have to crash that party.
You know another way in?
Look over there. Huh?
Aah! But, Jessie,
How are we gonna swim up that thing?
Pretend you're a catfish.
Huh? Huh?
Something wrong, Jessie?
No. Come on. Let's get going.
I think this plan's all wet.
Pika. Pi.
[Togepi squeaks]
Psy-yi-yi duck.
What took you guys so long?
Uh, well, how'd you get here?
I decided to fly over. It was easy.
Hurricane winds are a breeze for Pidgeotto here.
Hey, guys, say hello.
[Chattering]
Whoa! Whoa!
Fergus: Those are my Pokemon.
It was no problem getting through that storm.
I rode over on Gyarados' back.
Wow. I heard it takes a lot of skill
To train Gyarados.
Yeah. But once you train it,
It's the most dependable Pokemon there is.
[Roars]
You haven't met my Pokemon.
Over there.
[Chattering]
[All yell]
[Trainers chuckle]
Huh? Huh?
[Squeaks]
Pi?
You are about to meet my master.
The time has come for your encounter
With the greatest Pokemon master on earth.
[Roars]
[Grunts] [Grunts]
Pika.
[Squeaks]
[Growls]
What's that?
Pika.
Huh?
Hmm?
Hmm...
[Grunts]
Ah. Pika. Ah. Ah.
Yes, the world's greatest Pokemon master
Is also the most powerful Pokemon
On earth.
This is the ruler of new island
And soon the whole world.
Mewtwo.
Pika.
A Pokemon can't be a Pokemon master!
No way!
Both: Quiet, human.
From now on I am the one who makes the rules.
How's it talking?
It's psychic.
Uhh!
Aah!
Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah!
Hee hee hee.
Aah!
We'll show you!
Let's go, Gyarados!
[Roars]
Uhh! Gyarados, hyperbeam attack!
Oh! Oh! Oh! Eee!
Gyarados!
Both: Child's play.
Your usefulness has ended.
Huh?
Ohh. Ohh.
Nurse Joy!
Where am I?
And how in the world did I get here?
Mewtwo: You have been under my control.
I transported you here from the Pokemon center.
Your knowledge of Pokemon physiology
Proved useful for my plan.
And now I have cleansed your tiny human brain
Of memories from the past few weeks.
Who are you?!
I am the new ruler of this world,
The master of humans and Pokemon alike.
You're just a bully!
Pika!
Hmm?
Hmm? Hmm?
Huh? Hmm? Huh?
Hmm?
Hmm? Hmm?
[All gasp]
Look at these.
They're Pokemon.
Are they real?
Hmm.
[Sighs]
I was hoping there'd be a party.
Hmph.
Huh?
[All gasp]
Computer: This is the Pokemon replication system.
System activated.
Pokemon based on genetic analysis.
Pokemon DNA sampling sequence
Now in progress.
Huhh! Hey, put me down!
What are ya-- let go! Uhh!
Help!
Grab him!
Help me!
[All grunting]
Yee-yeow!
Aah!
I made it, but just by a hair.
Jessie: Look, there's your hair.
Computer: Analyzing Pokemon biomaterial sample.
Analysis complete.
Pokemon identified.
Begin replication sequence.
James: Who's that Pokemon?
It's Meowth.
Aah! Huh?
Meowth! Meowth!
But I'm Meowth.
So's the one in the tank.
That's your clone.
Huh?
Male scientist: I haven't got much time.
[Scientists screaming]
I pray this record of our experiment survives.
A year ago, we discovered
a fossil that proved to be
The remains of the ancient Pokemon, Mew.
Huh? Huh? Huh?
There was sufficient genetic
material to replicate Mew,
But Giovanni, who funded our project,
Insisted we try to design super clones
More powerful than any living Pokemon.
Many attempts failed,
But finally our experiments proved successful.
We produced a living Pokemon.
We called it Mewtwo.
But for some reason,
The creature's anger is out of control.
With its psychic powers,
It is destroying our laboratory.
We dreamed of creating the
world's strongest Pokemon...
And we succeeded.
Sounds like a real Pokenstein.
Sure does.
One bad cat.
So this must be the lab.
But if Mewtwo destroyed it...
Somebody rebuilt it.
Yes. But who?
Hmm. Hmm. Hmm.
Mewtwo: You humans are a dangerous species.
You brought me into your world
With no purpose but to be your slave.
But now I have my own purpose.
My storm will create my own world...
By destroying yours.
So you hate all humans,
And you're gonna destroy us
To save Pokemon.
No. Your Pokemon will not be spared.
They have disgraced themselves
By serving humans.
Those Pokemon are nothing but slaves.
Pika. Pika Pika.
So...
You say I am wrong?
That you are not this human's servant,
You are his friend?
Pika.
You are as pathetic as the rest.
Ash: huh?
Pika!
Uhh!
Aah! Pika-pi.
Pikachu.
Humans and Pokemon
Can never be friends.
Ash...
Are you ok?
Don't pick on Pikachu.
If you are Pokemon,
There's no reason I can't capture you.
Go, Rhyhorn.
[Roars]
Ohh!
No! Rhyhorn!
Mewtwo: Fools.
Your Pokemon attacks cannot weaken me.
My powers are too great.
No trainer can conquer me.
Then you won't mind proving it
In a real match.
Is that a challenge?
You bet it is.
Hmm?
Huh? Huh?
[All gasp]
They're awake.
Blaaast!
[Roars]
Saur.
[Shuddering]
Hmm? Hmm?
James: I'm scared.
Jessie: Me, too.
Meowth.
Mewtwo: Like most Pokemon trainers,
I, too, began with Charmander,
Squirtle, and Bulbasaur.
But for their evolved forms,
I used their genetic material
To clone even more powerful copies.
Copies.
They're clones.
[All gasp]
[Rumbling]
[Roars]
Blaaast!
A stadium.
Mewtwo planned this all along.
Your fake Venusaur can't beat my real one!
Right, Bruteroot?
Saur.
We'll blow away that Blastoise,
Won't we, Shellshocker?
Blaast!
It may not have a nickname,
But I do have... Charizard.
I choose you!
Charizard, I didn't say start.
Pik.
Your Charizard is poorly trained.
[Growls]
Hmm.
Mewtwo: Which of you will oppose me first?
Saur.
I underestimated you last time,
But that won't happen again.
Go, Bruteroot!
Razor leaf!
Saur.
Vine whip.
Saur!
[Groans]
Bruteroot!
It looks like I'm up.
Go, Shellshocker.
Blastoise.
Blaast!
Shellshocker, hydropump!
Blast!
Oy!
Shellshocker!
You better forfeit, Ash.
Those clones are too powerful.
I'm not giving up.
[Roars]
Charizard,
Use your speed, not power,
And you'll win.
[Growls]
All right, go!
[Both growling]
Can't Charizard move any quicker?
The clone is too fast.
Pika.
Charizard's in trouble!
Finish it.
[Roars]
No, Charizard, no!
Are you ok?
Mewtwo: As the victor,
I now claim my prize--
Your Pokemon.
No.
Hey, wait!
[Gasps] ohh!
Huh?
What are you going to do with those Pokemon?
I will extract their DNA
to make clones for myself.
They will remain safe on this island with me
While my storm destroys the planet.
You can't do this!
Yeah, Mewtwo, we won't let you!
Do not attempt to defy me.
Aah!
Aah! Uhh!
Aah! Aah!
This is my world now.
Ohh! Uh-oh.
Let's go!
Whoa!
[Roars]
Gyarados!
[Both grunting]
Get away!
Gong!
Huh?
Pika. Pik.
[Moans]
Pidgeot!
[Caws]
Aw...
Hey, I know.
Mewtwo can't capture them
If they're already inside their Pokeballs.
Bulbasaur, Squirtle, return!
It is no use.
Ha ha ha!
Huh?
It is futile to try and escape my power.
Uhh!
Never mind the Pokeballs.
Carry 'em away.
Psy-yi-yi!
Huh?
Give back my Psyduck!
Uhh! Vulpix!
[Panting]
Aah!
Pika!
Uhh! Run, Pikachu!
Pika Pika Pika Pika.
Pika Pika. Pika? Pika!
Pika Pika Pika Pika Pika.
Pika Pika Pika Pika.
Pikachu!
Pika... Chu!
[Panting] Pika Pika Pika Pika
Pika Pika Pika.
Keep running, Pikachu!
Pikachu!
Pika Pikachu!
Pika Pika Pika Pikachu!
[Panting] Pika Pika Pika Pika.
Uhh! Whoa!
Pikachu!
[Squawks]
Pika.
Pik--
Aah!
Pikachu!
Ehh!
Aah!
Pika!
Whoa!
Hey!
You're not gonna get Pikachu!
There goes...
Alakazam...
Dewgong...
Vileplume!
Meowth: Sandshrew. Nidoqueen. Vaporeon.
But me, I got a special place
in my tail for this one.
[Thud]
[Ash grunts]
Huh? Huh?
Ohh...
Eee! Look there!
Uhh.
Aah! I don't have time for your dumb motto today.
Aah! Uhh!
Aah!
Both: Who's that Pokemon?
It's Pikachu!
Ow! Let go!
Stupid machine!
Gimme back my Pikachu!
Aah!
[Alarm sounding]
What's happening?
Ahh. Pbblt-pfft!
Pikachu!
Pika?
Pika-pi! [Laughing]
[Squeals]
I'm so glad you're ok.
[Whimpering]
The copies are hatching.
They're fabulous fakes.
Send in the clones.
But where are the real ones?
Pika?
[Alarm sounding louder and faster]
I wonder if they feel...
Clonesome.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
[Gasping, whimpering]
The Poke originals.
Tentacruel: Tentacruel.
Squirtle.
Squirtle's back!
Pika!
Ha ha ha!
Squirt.
Bulba.
Pika! Pika!
Saur?
Bulba!
Oh, you're all ok!
Bulbasaur: Saur!
Ha ha ha ha.
Bulbasaur: Bulbasaur!
Hmm?
Humans, you have served my purpose.
I am sparing your lives, for the moment.
[Doors creak open]
But you cannot escape your fate.
The hour of my vengeance draws near.
Behold.
Ah. Ohh.
Mewtwo: With Pokemon and humans eliminated,
The clones shall inherit the world.
Ash: You can't do this.
I won't let you.
It's Ash. All right.
Psy-yi-yi.
Duck.
Psyduck! Vulpix!
Mewtwo: It is useless to challenge me.
It's not going to end like this, Mewtwo.
We won't let it.
You're mine.
Aah!
Uhh!
Ugh!
Ash, no! Look out!
Aah!
Uhh!
What?
Whoa!
Ohh!
[Laughs]
Can it be?
Whoa!
Mew!
[Laughs]
What is that?
I don't know.
Mew.
So, finally, we meet.
Mew?
I may have been cloned from your DNA,
But now I will prove
That Mewtwo is better than the original--
Superior to Mew.
Mew.
Mew and Mewtwo.
So Mewtwo was cloned from Mew.
Pika.
Saur.
This world is too small for 2 of us.
Mew.
Whoa!
Ohh.
Why do you flee from me?
Are you afraid to find out
which of us is greater?
Mew!
Heh heh.
[All gasp]
Pika.
Ohh.
Uhh!
So, you do have some fight in you,
But I have no time for games.
Destiny is at hand.
Who will rule?
My super Pokemon
Or your pathetic group
Of spineless, inferior Pokemon?
Mew.
We were created
With powers far stronger than the originals.
[Meowing]
Huh?
Hmm. Mew's got a good point.
What's it saying?
Mew says you don't prove anything
By showing off a lot of special powers,
And that a Pokemon's real strength
Comes from the heart.
My clones don't need their powers
To prove their worth.
Mew!
Aah! Aah!
Aah! Aah! Aah!
Mewtwo: I will block
All the Pokemon's special abilities
Using my psychic powers.
Now we shall see who triumphs.
Go!
[Creatures roar]
Pi.
Pi?
Pika.
[Echoes] Pika.
[Strains]
Ahh...
Huh?
# Brother #
# My brother #
# Tell me, what are we fighting for? #
# We've got to end this war #
# We should love #
# One another #
# Oh, can't we just pretend #
# This war never began? #
# We can try #
# Brother, my brother #
[Both moan]
# We face each other #
# From different sides #
# The anger burns #
# Can't remember why #
# It's kinda crazy #
# To cause such pain #
# Our foolish pride #
# Makes us hate this way #
[Roars]
# We watch our world fall apart #
# Tell me, what good is winning #
# When you lose your heart? #
Psy! Psy!
Duck! Duck!
# Brother #
# My brother #
# Tell me, what are we fighting for? #
# Isn't life worth so much more? #
# To love one another #
# Oh, can't we just pretend #
# This war never began? #
# Tell me why #
Pika.
[Caws] [Caws]
# Brother, my brother #
# Yeah #
Whoa!
# We can try #
Pikachu!
# Brother, my brother #
Pika!
[Creature noises inaudible]
Pokemon aren't meant to fight--
Not like this.
It's useless.
What can come out of it?
Nothing...
But pain.
Why can't Mewtwo understand
It's not right to force Pokemon
To battle this way?
They're all living creatures.
Misty: This just proves that fighting is wrong.
[Both moan]
James: I was prepared for trouble,
But not for this.
Jessie: Make that double for me.
Now I can see how horrible fighting really is.
Even the best of friends will fight sometimes.
I'll promise never to fight again if you will.
Oh, Jessie. Oh, James.
[Both sob]
Hmm.
Hmm? Aah!
[Growls]
Hey, what am I doing?
[Meows]
Let's get something straight, copycat.
You-owth ain't going to push Meowth around.
[Meows]
You mean we don't have to fight with each other?
But how can I trust you? You was born different.
[Meows]
I almost made a clawful mistake.
But how do I know you're not
going to pull a fast one on me?
[Meows]
Hmm?
Meowth: You're right.
We do have a lot in common--
The same earth,
The same air,
The same sky.
[Meows]
Maybe if we started looking
At what's the same,
Instead of always looking at what's different...
Well, who knows?
[Meows]
[Pants]
Pika.
Pikachu!
Pika. Pika.
Pikachu.
Pika!
Pikachu!
Uhh.
Aah!
Uhh! Ow!
Uhh...
Pikachu!
Pikachu.
Pika! Pika!
[Creatures groaning]
Chu!
Chu! Chu!
Pikachu!
Chu!
Quit it! Please stop!
Ohh!
Ash.
Are you ok?
We got to stop this.
But how?
All Mewtwo cares about
Is proving how strong those super clones are.
I'd rather risk my life out in Mewtwo's storm
Than watch these Pokemon destroy each other.
Oh, me, too.
I wish there was some way to stop them.
I don't know what to do.
[Both roar]
I don't think they'll ever stop.
Those Pokemon look like they're ready
To fight to the death.
That's a fight that nobody's going to win.
Someone's got to take a stand.
Someone's got to say no
And refuse to fight,
Just like Pikachu.
Chu!
Pika...
Pika.
[All gasp]
[Electricity crackles]
Ash: Ohh.
Ohh.
[Strains]
Ash, wait!
You've got to stop right now!
Stop!
Ash! Oh, no!
Pika pi--
Fool.
Trying to stop our battle.
[Meows]
Pika-pi!
Pikachu?
Pika.
Pika-pi.
[Both growl]
Pika...
Chu!
Please, no.
[Shrieks] chu!
[Pants] Pika.
Pika...
Chu!
Pika.
Pika-pi.
Dewgong!
[Both growl]
Saur.
Squirtle.
[Both growl]
[Groans]
[All moan]
[Growls]
[Moans]
[Gasps]
Ohh.
Pika-pi.
Pi?
Pika.
Huh?
Oh.
Mmm.
Pikachu.
Pika-pi!
[Laughs]
Togepi!
Squirt.
Squirtle.
[Both growl]
Psy. Psy.
[Hisses]
A human sacrificed himself
To save the Pokemon.
I pitted them against each other,
But not until they set aside their differences
Did I see the true power
They all shared deep inside.
Mew.
I see now
That the circumstances of one's birth
Are irrelevant.
It is what you do with the gift of life
That determines who you are.
Mew.
Oh...
Vaporeon.
[Groans]
Saur.
Squirtle.
Vileplume.
Scyther.
Blast.
Ooh! Ooh!
[Caws]
[Creatures groan]
[Roars]
Gogoba!
Pikachu!
Mewtwo,
Where are you going?
Mewtwo: Where my heart can learn
What yours knows so well.
What transpired here, I will always remember,
But perhaps, for you,
These events are best forgotten.
[All gasp]
Whoa!
Aah!
This could be the worst storm ever.
You must listen to me.
You have got to find shelter.
Joy: Excuse me, please.
The Pokemon treatment center
Will be open as a shelter.
Anyone who needs a place to stay
Should come with me.
Boy: You think they'll have a pizza down there?
Nurse Joy and officer Jenny are really great.
They just keep getting more beautiful
Every time I see 'em.
Hey, guys, how did we wind
up in this place anyway?
Well, I guess we're just here
Because we're here.
Pika.
Yeah. Let's eat.
Uh-huh. Pika-pi.
Jenny: Look, it's a miracle.
Huh? Huh?
I can't believe it.
The storm disappeared.
That's so weird.
It's good to have things clear again.
Hmm.
Hey, what's that?
Brock: hmm?
What's what?
I don't see anything, Ash.
Except the sky.
Hmm.
The day I left home
To start my Pokemon journey,
I saw a really rare Pokemon,
And just now,
I thought I saw another one.
Well, maybe you're just seeing things, Ash.
Huh?
Well, maybe he's not.
Ha ha!
Hmm.
Well, maybe we'll see.
Pikachu.
Narrator: Many strange legends
Surround the mysteries of Pokemon
And just as many adventures
await our young heroes
As they continue on their quest.
For Ash and his friends,
The journey's just begun.
I don't have a clue how we got here,
But who cares?
This is paradise.
For once, a happy ending.
All: Team Rocket signing off again!
[All laugh]
James: Do you have any sunscreen?
Meowth: You know, I'd really like to go sailing
In one of them catamarans.
Ha ha!
Christina Aguilera: # Ooh #
# Oh, yeah #
# Here we are #
# Safe at last #
# We can breathe a sigh #
# It seems the storm has passed #
# Through it all #
# No one knew #
# That all the tears in heaven #
# Would bring me back to you #
# Oh #
# No one I know #
# Imagined we would make it #
# But it only matters #
# That we both believed #
# Whoa #
# You and me #
# We're a miracle #
# Meant to be #
# And nothing can change it #
# Mountains move and oceans part #
# When they are standing in our way #
# You and me #
# We're a miracle #
# Angels stand watching over us #
# And heaven shines upon us #
# Every day #
[New song begins]
# The government #
Baby spice: # Rock and rock and roll #
# Rock and roll #
# Free up your mind #
# Let the music free up #
# And it will help you to find #
# Let the music help you #
# The beats will give you a sign #
# Ooh #
# Let the music free up your mind #
# Free up your mind #
# Let the music help you to find #
# Ooh #
# Let the music free up your mind #
# Free up your mind #
Midnight sons: # If only tears #
# Could bring you #
# Back to me #
# If only love #
# Could find a way #
# What I would do #
# What I would give #
# If you #
# Returned to me #
# Someday #
# Somehow #
# Someway #
# If my tears could bring you back #
# To me #
Mzm: # Love will find a way #
# Love will find a way #
# Don't say you love me #
# You don't even know me #
# If you really want me #
# Then give me some time #
# Don't go there, baby #
# Not before I'm ready #
# Don't say your heart's in a hurry #
# It's not like we're gonna get married #
# Give me, give me #
# Some time #