- Addic7ed.com -
[Music]
[Groans]
What the heck just happened?
Lars!
You saved us!
You stopped the Robonoids, but ...
but one of them exploded,
and ... and you weren't moving,
and I started crying.
[Gasps]
I brought you back to life!
It was an accident.
I mean, I probably would've
done that on purpose
if I had known I could do that,
but I didn't really ask
your permission, so I'm sorry.
Back to life?
So I was... away from life?
Aah!
I'm pink!
Ah! I know.
Do you feel okay?
I don't really know.
- But your body, are you sore?
- No.
- Are you tired?
- Do you feel good?
- No.
- Do you feel bad?
- No!
I guess I just feel
really freaked out.
Well, I am, too, so at least
we're on the same page here.
[Whooshing]
They're back.
Those shattering Robonoids
are back!
Quickly.
Block the entrance.
- Lars, you stay here and rest.
- All right.
I predict Lars will change in hue.
What a mystery!
[All grunting]
Whoa, strong.
[Steven grunting]
Is this
gonna be enough?
[Whirring]
They seem
to have overlooked us
for the time being.
Quickly,
block the entrance!
As long as I'm here, they're
gonna keep coming after us.
It's true.
This was a horrible plan.
Should we try to find
a new hiding spot?
No, no, no!
If we leave this cavern,
we'll be
completely exposed.
But if we stay here,
they'll find us for sure.
So, we either stay here
and get caught...
Or we go out there
and get caught.
So, wait,
am I a zombie now?
No.
Well...no!
You can talk,
and zombies can't do that.
I must've healed you.
I've healed people before,
just never this much.
Just admit it, Steven!
I'm a zombie!
Oh, I know.
A zombie wouldn't
have a heartbeat.
[Heart beating slowly]
That's, uh,
pretty slow.
But I think we can rule out
pink zombie.
Thank the stars.
What's a zombie?
I can't believe humans
just change color like this.
They don't.
Well, I guess if you get
really cold, you turn blue,
and if you get really
embarrassed, you turn red.
So what does pink mean?
Is Lars gonna explode
or something?
Maybe then Lars will reform
with a different color.
I'm sure whatever color
Lars chooses
will be lovely.
But why am I pink?
[Groans]
Even your hair
is different.
Aah!
What was that?
Huh?
It, like, lit up, right?
You saw it, too.
Uh, yeah.
What did you do?
Do it again.
Why is it doing that?
Lars, I think I know
what this is.
There's something I can try,
but no.
You don't want me
going in your head.
You're going to
possess me again?
No.
It would be more literal.
- Then what is it?
- Forget it.
Look, Steven,
I'm not gonna get mad, okay?
I trust you.
Just help me out here.
If I've got magic hair now,
I want to know.
Everyone stand back.
All right,
now just bend down.
Like this?
Now, you might feel
a slight foot in your head.
Wait, what?
[Grunting]
[All gasp]
What is happening?
They're fusing!
They're fusing, right?
You're doing great,
Lars.
Uh, okay.
[Inhales deeply]
[Music]
[Gasps]
Ah. I'm home.
I'm home!
Guys?
Where are they?
Water!
Ahh.
[Gulping]
[Stomach gurgles]
[Gasps]
Food.
Life is beautiful!
Got to bring some back for Lars.
Wish I could tell everyone
I'm okay.
Oh, Lion.
So you were ...
[Sighs]
Gosh, there ... there's so much
I want to ask you.
If only you could talk.
Thanks, buddy.
[Gasps]
- Aah!
[Groans]
Sorry, Lars.
So what happened?
What's in my head?
- Home.
- Wha?
Everyone, I've made
an amazing discovery!
I just traveled back
to planet Earth
by going through
Lars' head!
You went back to Earth?
What the heck?
Is my head
like a wormhole?
No, it's way simpler
than that.
You see,
I have a pink pet lion
who belonged to my mom
when she was still here,
and it turns out
I can go into his mane,
and it transports me
to a magical dimension
where my mom kept a bunch of
artifacts on a hill with a tree,
and for some reason,
I can't breathe in there.
But anyway,
when I went into Lars' head,
I got transported
to the same magical dimension,
but it was a new part of it,
but since the two are connected,
I could reach the portal
that leads out of Lion's mane,
which is back on Earth!
Uh...
Here,
I brought you some food.
Huh? Thanks,
but I-I'll save it for later.
But aren't you hungry?
Maybe you only eat magical
lizards now like Lion.
A-Are you hungry for lizards?
No, I do not want
a lizard.
But you haven't eaten
in days.
I know.
There must be pink magic
in my guts now or something.
What is this box?
It's juice.
We drink it back on Earth.
- What?
- That's impossible.
- There's no way.
- Unh-unh.
Steven's back.
That can't be.
I'm incredulous.
Why can't it be?
Everyone knows
that the Earth...
Was decimated
by the Diamond attack!
Sorry.
It's not like that.
The Diamonds did attack,
but there are still Gems
living on Earth,
and the planet's
full of life.
It grew the potatoes
that became these chips
and grew the wheat
that eventually became the flour
that eventually became the bread
that eventually became
this sandwich!
- Sand...
- Wich?
But why would Gems
still live there?
Because the Earth is a place
where we can be ourselves.
We can live freely without
having to hide who we are.
Live freely?
Without
having to hide?
That sounds wonderful.
It is.
And now that we have this
portal, we can all go there.
All?
How am I supposed to go
through my own head?
Oh.
Hmm.
[Grunting]
Stop!
You're gonna break my elbow!
Okay, so that didn't work, but
I'm sure there's another way.
No, no, look.
I get it.
Everyone just go,
and I'll stay here.
There's no other way out.
I'm it.
The Earth is way better
than this.
There's no robots
flying around.
Just seagulls that fly
in front of the sunset
and it's beautiful!
Just go, you'll see.
I took it for granted,
so don't pass up this chance.
Well, if you insist.
We won't do it.
Not if it means
leaving you behind.
What?! I'm trying to perform
a beautiful act over here.
We know this planet.
We've been hiding
in these tunnels for eons.
You'll need us
to help you get around.
Besides, us off colors
stick together.
We'll get to Earth
another way.
We'll find
an alternate route.
But you've
got to go back.
But it doesn't feel right
to just leave you here.
You said yourself
that everyone on this planet
is out to get you.
You won't be safe
until you're back on Earth.
But, Lars ...
Don't argue with me!
You're always trying
to help me.
You brought me
back to life.
Just let me be somebody
who deserved it.
All right,
I'll tell everyone you're okay.
I'll be back.
I can bring whatever you need.
- Be careful, okay?
- We will.
We can't leave without Lars!
We'll see you on Earth, I hope.
No, no, no.
We will!
[Music]
Um, if you
could just...
Oh, yeah.
This is hopeless.
[Gasps]
We'll never get that dropship
to fly, and we're losing time!
Who knows what they're doing
to Steven.
Hi, Steven.
What are we going to d...
I'm back!
[Music]
[Laughs]
- Addic7ed.com -