- - Addic7ed.com - -
[Static]
♪ But I'd really rather be ♪
♪ Eating your brain ♪
- Steven: Whoo-hoo!
- Just another hot track from
Sadie Killer and the Suspects.
- How's it sound, Sour Cream?
- Here, check it out.
Buck: Hey, Steven.
How's the footage coming?
[Chuckles] Great!
Your documentation
of our humble beginnings
will be important when we become
a pop-culture phenomenon.
Okay, but why are you recording
it on that giant shoe box?
It's my dad's old camcorder.
These are your early days.
The footage has to look old.
I think I could get a more
guttural scream on the chorus
if I rest my voice a little.
[Footsteps approach]
Barb: Sadie!
Could you give me
a hand with the gro... Oh!
Didn't realize you had
practice today. Hey, kids!
- Hi, Ms. Miller.
Steven: Hi, Barb!
Uh-oh. There's a film crew!
Good thing us Millers
only have good angles, huh?
Mo-o-o-o-o-m!
Okay, okay. I know the rule.
I'll stay out of your hair.
It's okay.
We're done for the night.
You know you can play
while I'm in the house.
It won't bother me. I'm old.
I can't hear anything!
Heh! Okay. Thanks, Mom.
What?! Huh?!
Can't hear a thing!
Let me know if you kids want
to stick around for dinner.
I'm making a salad
that's mostly cheese.
Okay! Thanks, Mom!
[Rock music playing
on headphones]
You said this is Sadie singing?
Steven: Uh-huh.
This is good stuff!
You should see them live.
Sadie has this
alter ego, and ...
Huh?
Uh, you should see them live!
- What?!
- See them live! It's awesome!
[Mid-tempo rock music plays]
♪ Teens by day,
we're all right ♪
but every night we're ♪
♪ Sadie Killer
and the Suspects ♪
♪ Whoa-oh-oh ♪
♪ Sadie Killer
and the Suspects ♪
♪ Don't be scared,
it's the afternoon ♪
but pretty soon we'll be... ♪
♪ Sadie Killer
and the Suspects ♪
♪ Whoa-oh-oh ♪
♪ Sadie Killer
and the Suspects ♪
♪ The moon is out,
I'm feeling strange ♪
♪ It's making me shout,
it's making me change ♪
♪ You better watch out,
it's going to get loud ♪
♪ I'm killing the stage,
I'm killing the crowd ♪
And you're next.
[Plays note]
Whoa! That was great!
Sadie, you transform into
a totally different person.
Steven: Yeah.
No more Sadie Miller.
She's Sadie Killer.
Heh heh. Yeah.
It feels...kind of freeing.
I can tell!
And this whole look you guys
have going is really fun!
Nice wolf man, Buck.
I'm a witch's cat.
We know
our costumes look cheap.
But when we make it big,
we're going to have the finest
tombstone hats money can buy.
But that's a long ways off.
We're still mostly playing,
uh, well, basements.
That's where everyone starts.
Now you just got to work on
the stuff that isn't music ...
booking shows, making merch,
getting the word out.
Steven: Dad! You know how
to do all that stuff!
You could help them!
What, like,
be their manager?
Yeah!
You taught me
everything I know, Mr. U.
I think you'd be a great manager.
- Yeah!
- Yeah, come on!
Ha! I'll take the job!
Yeah! Yeah!
Thanks, Mr. Universe!
And so it begins ...
our rise to stardom,
followed by the inevitable infighting
and creative disagreements
that will tear us apart in a
beautiful explosion of emotions.
Don't worry.
That won't happen.
Ah, shoot.
Hey, Sunshine!
It's your old friend,
Mr. Universe.
Are you still booking all the
coolest bands at your club?
Well, listen to this!
[Rock music playing]
Oh, sorry. It's probably hard
to hear over the phone.
I'll e-mail you a link.
Yeah. [Laughs]
Talk to you soon.
Who was that?
Oh, Sunshine Justice.
She's an old music buddy that
owns a venue in Empire City.
[Computer dings]
Oh! She replied.
"This is the absolute worst
recording I've ever heard.
It's a shame because
I love the song.
Let's get these kids on stage
with some decent equipment"?
- They've got a gig!
- Whoo!
I'll e-mail her back
right away!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
It's a big stage,
so you're gonna have
a lot of space we can fill up.
Isn't that fog machine
really expensive?
The Fog Of War is one of
the best units out there.
Go big! It's on my tab.
When you say, "Big,"
you mean, like,
glow sticks in every color?
Bigger! I'm talking lasers!
Lasers?!
Special delivery.
I think this will get us through
the show tomorrow and then some.
Check it.
Sadie: Oh-ho-ho!
Nice!
Scary and stylish.
Huh?
The Fog Of War
and our lasers...
and Barb!
These all got your name
on them, Greg.
You building a new car wash
or something?
[Chuckles] It's all for
Sadie Killer and the Suspects.
Huh?
Your daughter's band.
I'm their manager.
What are you talking about,
an old duffer like you
managing a band?
[Chuckles]
Well, I may be old,
but that didn't stop me
from getting them a gig in ...
In some no-name city.
It's not a big deal.
"Sadie Killer and the Suspects,
live at Empire Ci..."
[Gasps] My girl is playing
in Empire City?!
This is a huge deal!
Oh, my gosh. Geez.
If you need to carry all
this stuff and your instruments,
I-I can probably use
the mail truck if I ask nice.
And I can definitely
use it if I don't ask.
Oh! And you'll need
snacks for the road, and ...
Mom!
We've talked about this!
Steven: Uh, Sadie?
The band is my thing,
and I just want to be able
to do it on my own.
Right, right.
You need your space.
I understand.
You kids be safe
and have a good show, huh?
[Engine starts]
Ready the cords.
Here I go.
Aah!
[Laughter]
Ohh. Ugh.
My mom used to be
so into my life.
It was suffocating.
But now I get
to be Sadie Killer,
and it's something
that's totally mine,
and I know she's just waiting
to get her hands on it.
Wow. That's so funny.
How is it funny?
It drives me nuts!
Oh, no. It's just
back in the day,
my parents didn't want
anything to do with my music.
They thought I was
throwing my life away.
They never came
to one of my shows.
They never even wanted
to hear about them.
Really?
It's kind of amazing
that your mom
is excited about your band.
It's just
really nice to see.
Yeah. Yeah.
I-I guess you're right.
Jenny: Are you ready, Sadie Killer?
- Yeah!
- Aah!
I'm so excited!
It's our big first show!
- Yeah!
- Me, too.
- The venue!
I love enthusiasm.
And we got about six more
cameras in the back of the van.
What do you mean, you don't
know how to tie a tie?
Yeah. Like, didn't
your dad teach you?
He used to wear them
every day.
They were clip-ons.
Steven: Sadie! What's up?
Are you nervous?
No, no. I'm just, um ...
just getting ready.
Sounds like a big
crowd out there.
Wait. Is that...
Mom?!
Does she think she can just
show up in some wacky disguise
and I won't know it's her?
It's so obvious!
Maybe she should have gotten
some costume tips from you.
Greg: Okay, guys.
You're on in 5.
[Slow music plays]
[Tempo increases]
[Music continues]
♪ I used to be sick ♪
♪ Sick and tired ♪
♪ Delirious, dizzy, terrified ♪
♪ But I'm suddenly up
and out of bed ♪
♪ You'd never believe
I was almost... ♪
♪ Why can't you see me? ♪
♪ I think I might be ♪
♪ A gh-gh-gh-ghost ♪
♪ Awwwww! ♪
♪ Can't you see that I exist ♪
♪ And I don't need an exorcist ♪
♪ To let me out? ♪
♪ Look at me, and I'll appear ♪
♪ Why can't you see
that I'm right here? ♪
♪ That I'm right here ♪
♪ Why can't you see me? ♪
♪ I think I might be ♪
♪ A gh-gh-gh-ghost ♪
[Echoing] # Ghost #
[Scattered cheers
and applause]
[Instrumental break]
[Distorted voice]
# I'm calling you from #
♪ The other side ♪
[Song ends,
cheers and applause]
Greg:
You were all so amazing!
Yeah, we were!
Sadie, you nailed
that ending.
Sadie: Oh!
- Hey, Ma!
- Sunshine Justice!
How you been, Greg?
Where'd you find these kids?
Reminds me of your
old space gimmick,
except people
actually like it.
Hey!
[Chuckles]
I'm just kidding.
You were very ahead
of your time.
But Sadie Killer
and the Suspects ...
that crowd was going crazy.
You're really something.
You kids are welcome to play
at the venue anytime.
- Aah! Aah! Aah!
- Oh, yeah!
[Snoring softly]
Steven:
You did great tonight!
Thanks.
So, how does it feel
to be a rock star?
Weird. I mean, good.
It's just...
I went all out thinking
my mom was at the show.
I can't believe I kind of
wanted her to be there.
Well, not even kind of.
I did.
There'll be other shows.
Why don't you tell her
about the next one?
Hey, Mr. Universe, let's play
our next show in Beach City.
I'll make it happen.
That's all, folks.
Thanks for watching.
- - Addic7ed.com - -
[Music]