♪ We ♪
♪ Are the Crystal ♪
♪ Gems ♪
♪ We'll always save the day ♪
♪ And if you think
we can't, we'll ♪
♪ Always find a way ♪
♪ That's why the people ♪
♪ Of this world ♪
♪ Believe in ♪
♪ Garnet ♪
♪ Amethyst ♪
♪ And Pearl ♪
And Steven!
*STEVEN UNIVERSE*
Season 05   Episode 17
Episode Title :
"Can't Go Back"
Sync corrections  by  srjanapala
Night, Peridot.
Nothing left to do but dream.
Hmm.
Steven!
Ste... ven!
Ronaldo,
it's the middle of the night.
You have to come
to the lighthouse.
I've found
something weird.
You've found something
weird every day
since my dad got you
that telescope.
I know. I'm amazing.
You won't believe
my latest discovery.
There's something
on the moon.
Can't you call Nanefua?
Not a fourth time.
Hmm.
This is the moon base.
It's always been there.
You have a moon base?!
I have so many questions.
One... Why didn't you tell me
about your moon base?
Two...
Take me to your moon base.
Three... Why does it
look like a barn?
It doesn't look like a...
Wait, what?
Lapis?
Whoa!
Thanks, Lion.
That super warp takes
a lot out of you, huh?
You and me both,
buddy.
You stay here and rest up,
okay?
Why would Lapis bring
the Barn to the moon?
Thought she wanted to get as far
away from Earth as possible.
Lapis?
Lapis Lazuli?
This is weird.
All the meep morps
are still here, but no Lapis.
Now, what is going on?
Lapis?
Lapis!
Steven.
Hup!
I can't believe it.
It's so good
to see you again.
Oh, really?
What's going on?
I-I thought you'd be halfway
across the galaxy by now.
Aren't you worried about
the Diamonds coming to attack?
I got... distracted.
By this orb thing?
What is it?
Promise
you won't judge me.
I sleep with a teddy bear.
No judgments.
Wha...
Wha-huh?
Beach City?
Please explain this to me.
This orb is
an observation device.
The Diamonds use them
to watch activity
on their colonies
from afar.
- Wow.
- Can I try?
Sure.
Whoa.
But, Lapis, what are
you using it for?
You're spying on us?
Well, I wouldn't
call it spying
because that would
make me feel bad.
Oh, Lapis.
I couldn't stand not knowing
what was going on.
I'm still terrified of
the Diamonds coming to Earth,
but I got just outside the
Milky Way and I felt so lonely.
So why didn't you
just come back?
I want to, but I just can't,
not after the way I left.
What would Peridot say?
What if the Diamonds show up?
What if something bad happens?
Well, what if
something good happens?
Uh, Lapis?
You okay?
♪ It all became so lovely ♪
♪ Those bluest skies
above me ♪
♪ Those funny feelings ♪
♪ I had never felt
before I met you ♪
♪ I thought
I'd stay a while ♪
♪ I tried to
learn to smile ♪
♪ So many colors
I had never even known ♪
♪ Maybe I'll find myself
sitting on that distant shore ♪
♪ Maybe I'm not alone ♪
♪ Then I see the colors
fading ♪
♪ Gentleness of light
escaping ♪
♪ Shadows of my fear invading ♪
♪ Have I seen this all before ♪
♪ I know that
there's something residing ♪
♪ A terror deep inside me ♪
♪ I couldn't understand
how you could be so bold ♪
♪ Maybe I'll find myself
smiling on that distant shore ♪
♪ Maybe I'm not alone ♪
I might have overreacted
about the Diamonds.
You really think
they're coming?
I don't even know anymore.
I've done so much
because I was afraid.
I left Peridot behind.
I took the Barn
and her morps.
Hey,
at least she has Pumpkin.
I was so sure the Diamonds
would destroy my new home
that I did it myself.
It's like I'm back
inside the mirror,
except I put myself here.
Oh, the moon's not so bad.
Are you kidding?
The moon sucks.
There's nothing here.
Maybe I'm tired
of running away.
Maybe I'd rather
be with everyone
and be in danger
than be safe and alone.
They'd be glad
to have you back.
I don't know.
If I went back now,
there's no way things
could go back to how they were.
Yeah,
but that's all right.
Things would just
be different.
What do you mean?
Well, what if you weren't
way out in the country?
You could drop the Barn
on the beach.
Then we'd all
be neighbors.
I'd come over to borrow
a cup of a sugar
and you'd be like,
"What's that?"
When you go back,
we should all hang out more.
Huh, when I go back.
This is what you wanted.
Lapis?
You begged us for
a colony of your own,
and now all you want
to do is be rid of it.
First there were
too many Organics.
Then their cities were
too difficult to dismantle,
and...
And now these Crystal Gems.
We're tired of
your excuses, Pink.
The Diamonds!
This Rose Quartz
can't hurt you.
You can't be swayed
by a few unruly Gems.
Enough.
You must understand,
you are a Diamond.
Everyone on this planet
is looking to you.
You don't even
have to do anything.
Just smile and wave.
Show everyone you're unfazed
by this little uprising.
Your gems will fall into line,
and these Crystal Gems
will be no more.
As long as you
are there to rule,
this colony will be completed.
Mom's sword?
Is that...
Pearl?
Steven, are you okay?
Were you dreaming?
I... I saw the Diamonds.
What? What are you
talking about?
I dreamt about them.
They were right in this room.
What does that mean?
Are they coming?
I... I don't know.
What if they are?
What if they're close?
Why else would you see them?
Steven.
Ugh!
Lapis, hold on!
Ah!
Ahhh!
Where are you going?
As far from Earth
as I can!
I'm leaving.
You should be used
to that by now.
You don't have to run,
Lapis.
Just...
Just stay with us.
I don't know
what I was thinking.
I-I'm not like you
and your friends, Steven.
I can't just let go
of what happened to me.
I can't go through that
again.
Would you rather
be alone?
I'm sorry.
Wait!
Lion, I need you to
take me to Pearl.