- Garnet: # We #
- # Are the Crystal #
- Steven: # Gems #
- # we'll always save the day #
Steven: # and if you think we can't #
All: # we'll always find a way #
- # that's why the people #
- # of this world #
Garnet: # believe in... Garnet #
- # Amethyst #
- # and Pearl #
Steven: # And Steven! #
- - Addic7ed.com - -
Lars: Captain's log.
Star date, uh...
Thursday.
Space is really big.
Everything is messed up.
Our nova thrusters are busted.
And getting home
is taking forever.
Hey, Captain?
Should we be writing this down?
Uh, yeah!
[Music]
Who wants a party sub?!
What exactly
are we celebrating?
You guys beat Emerald.
And you rescued me and Connie
from the Jungle Moon.
And you have this
super fast ship,
so you'll be back
on Earth in no time.
It's only super fast
when it works!
Captain Lars...
I've finished...
rerouting...
Power from the gravity engine
to the nova thrusters?
Great! Twins, floor it
on the thrusters!
Right away, Captain.
Yes, Captain.
Aww!    Aww!
Aww!            Aww!
Captain Lars,
don't use the thrusters.
We're going to lose power!
Thanks, Padparadscha.
Hey, if we're going to be
drifting a while,
there's somebody
I'd like you all to meet.
[Groans]
Are they bigger
than that sandwich?
Maybe a few pickles bigger.
Bigger than you?
I mean,
they don't have to be.
Fine. Bring 'em over.
[Shing!]
[Whoosh!]
Twins!
Another...Steven?
There's more of you?!
[All gasp]
[Music]
Her eyes.
A fusion?
He's going to bring back
another Steven!
This is Garnet.
She leads the Crystal Gems
back on Earth.
Just look at you all!
You must be Rhodonite ...
a Ruby and a Pearl?
That must have been a story.
I want all the details.
[Chuckles nervously]
Eh.
And you must be
the Rutile Twins.
[Gasps] I've never seen
anyone like you before.
We were...made like this.
Fluorite. Whoa.
You're just, uh, beautiful.
And here's Padparadscha,
an orange Sapphire.
How rare.
I predict you're going to make
everyone uncomfortable.
It's not nice to make fun
of us like that.
Haven't you guys heard
a compliment before?
A what?
What's that?
You know, it's when someone says
something nice about you.
Who would say nice things
about Gems like us?
We're completely inappropriate,
and so are you.
We should all be ashamed.
Aw, Steven.
These Gems feel just like I did
before I met Rose Quartz.
- Both: Rose Quartz?
- Rose... Quartz?
You met Rose Quartz?
And your survived?
You guys know about Rose?
She was the Anit-Gem ...
an organic beast that burst
out of Earth's crust
and vowed to destroy all Gems!
No, no.
She was made from a vein
of hyper-defective quartz.
A malformed quartz
gone haywire.
Don't...be...silly.
Rose...Quartz...isn't...real.
You have it all wrong.
Rose Quartz?!
Of course that's how
they tell it on Homeworld.
Come on, everyone.
Let me tell you the story
of the real Rose Quartz.
It was Era 1.
The Diamonds, unique
in their flawlessness,
sought to expand their
perfection across the galaxy.
And it was for this purpose
that Pink Diamond
chose her first colony,
the planet Earth.
On Earth, every Gem was made
to serve Pink Diamond,
each with a role to play
in her world's perfect empire.
In comparison to their creator,
their existence was ordinary.
They were life-forms
only meant to fit their mold,
and no one had ever dared
to think otherwise ...
until there was Rose Quartz.
In stature, she was no different
than any other Quartz,
and for a time, she did her best
to carry out
her Diamond's bidding.
[Music]
However, she began to take
notice of her strange colony
and the life that existed there.
Curiosity
turned to appreciation.
Appreciation
turned to fondness.
And fondness...turned to love.
Soon she was unable
to keep her findings secret,
and she began asking
her fellow Gems
if they knew
of the life on Earth
and what they made of it.
She continued to pry her
fellow kindergartners
with questions so odd
that word of her eventually made
its way to Pink Diamond.
Rose Quartz
was summoned at once.
"Quartz," began Pink Diamond,
"What have you been
saying down there?"
"Why, Diamond," Rose pleaded,
"It has come to my attention
that your colony,
Earth, bears life.
While I know these organic
life-forms serve no purpose,
I ask that we leave this planet
and spare their lives."
Pink Diamond thought
for a moment
and then laughed,
a wicked, empty sound.
"You wish to save
these life-forms
at the expense of our own?
Ha! Don't be absurd.
Return to your post, and I will
forget your insolence."
And with that, Rose Quartz
was dragged back
to her kindergarten for duty.
Only Rose could no longer
stand to continue
aiding in the destruction
of Earth.
She had no choice.
She had to fight.
[Twinkle!]
[Music]
"Is this what you want ...
to inject, to build?
I've seen the life that exists
for itself, and it lives here.
Will you destroy it,
or will you join it?"
Rose's message
began to resonate,
to Pink Diamond's dismay.
Her colony was falling apart.
So, like a coward, she called
for her Diamond allies,
Yellow and Blue, to help.
But Rose also found herself
with allies,
other Gems that were cast out
for being wrong ...
a Pearl who belonged
to no one...
a Bismuth who built
weapons for rebels
instead of towers for tyrants...
an entirely new fusion
for not power but for love...
and countless others,
all inspired by Rose
to live for ourselves on Earth.
She was our leader.
And Earth was our precious home.
And those who fought to save it
became known as...
the Crystal Gems!
Unbelievable.
There were Gems like us?
Fighting.
For...their...freedom?
Yes, and we were fearless.
It was an impossible fight,
but we fought anyway.
And the more Gems who saw us,
the more who joined.
But Pink Diamond's forces
proved too strong.
Rose feared that soon she would
have nothing left to protect.
[Music]
Rose Quartz
drew her rebel blade...
[Shing! Crack!]
...and shattered Pink Diamond,
saving the Earth for all time
from her reign of terror.
Wow! That's incredible!
I don't believe it!
Your mom did all that?
That's awesome!
Wait. What about the rest?
What happened after that?
Garnet:
The other Diamonds were furious.
In a last-ditch attempt
to wipe out the rebellion,
the Diamonds launched
a direct attack against Earth,
and in their fury, they used
their powers to end the fighting
once and for all.
[Twinkle! Zap!]
[Music]
I predict this story
won't have a happy ending.
We were all told
different stories.
But they all ended
the same way.
With Rose Quartz...
being...defeated.
This new version of the story
is even worse!
So, she was great,
and they beat her?
What are we supposed
to get out of this ...
that we can never win?!
We haven't yet, but we can,
and we will.
They said they annihilated
Rose's rebellion,
but here we are.
They said they annihilated
all of you on Homeworld,
but here you are.
They think they have us
on the run,
but they're the ones that are
running from the truth.
And the truth is
we...are...everywhere!
But how many more of us
can there be?
Way more than you think!
I was only on Homeworld
for, like, an hour
before I ran in to you guys.
There must be Off Colors
all over the place.
Rose used to say there
was something about Earth ...
something that set Gems free.
But it's not just Earth.
Look at you.
Love, freedom ...
it's universal.
You all prove it every moment
you live as yourselves.
You can show everyone.
We...can do that?
Not while we're floating
out here like sitting ducks.
Fluorite, let's take
another look at that engine.
- Yes!
- Okay!
- Yeah!
- Fluorite: Lars.
Before we can activate
the thrusters,
we're going to need
to restart the core.
How do we do that?
We'll figure it out
together.
Hey, uh, Garnet?
When Connie and I were stranded
on the Jungle Moon, I ...
we ... saw something...
a vision...of...
Pink Diamond.
Hmm.
When Blue Diamond
came to Earth,
I had dreams where
I saw through her eyes
and I was crying her tears.
If I'm having the same dreams
about Pink Diamond,
what if that means
she's still out there?
She's gone, Steven.
Your mother
made sure of that.
But I felt such
a strong connection.
You have empathetic powers
that other Gems don't have.
You're unusual, Steven,
like them and like me.
It's not something to fear.
It's something to celebrate.
Come on, come on.
Oh, strange.
The core should have
come online by now.
I predict that Captain Lars will
be pressing the wrong button.
Oh.
Yes! We did it!
[Music]
Does that mean you can
get back to Earth?
Not...quite.
The nova thrusters
still need...repairs.
We can hit up the nearest
colony for parts.
Rhodonite, tell me
there's one nearby.
Well, we aren't far from one of
Yellow Diamond's asteroid mines.
But that place will be
crawling with Agates, Captain.
It's incredibly dangerous.
So are we.
Let's show 'em!
- - Addic7ed.com - -