- Garnet: # We #
- # Are the Crystal #
- Steven: # Gems #
- # we'll always save the day #
Steven: # and if you think we can't #
All: # we'll always find a way #
- # that's why the people #
- # of this world #
Garnet: # believe in... Garnet #
- # Amethyst #
- # and Pearl #
Steven: # And Steven! #
- Addic7ed.com -
Steven: We'll be fine!
I'll be right back.
I'm just gonna walk Connie out.
Don't worry! I'm not going
back into space or anything.
[Laughs]
They're never gonna
let me out of their sight again.
Connie?
Connie! I know you got to
get home and get some sleep,
but once you're all rested up,
I can't wait to tell you
about everything!
Being on Homeworld was crazy!
After I turned myself in,
they put me on trial!
And Lars was there.
We got chased by killer robots.
[Chuckles]
What a wild ride that was.
And uh...I'm really happy
to see you again.
Umm... a-are you happy
to see me, too?
Of course I'm happy
to see you, Steven.
Uh, but?
But how could you just
give yourself up like that?
Well, first,
I said I was my dad,
and then I said I was my mom.
[Scoffs] No.
I mean, you just gave up.
I had to.
They were gonna take
all those people.
They were gonna take you!
But what about our training?
Stevonnie.
Jam buds.
I believed in us.
We could have done it together.
This is different.
This whole thing was my fault,
but I knew that I could fix
it all if I turned myself in.
And look ...
No one got hurt.
Well, except for Lars,
but I saved him, too.
But... I'm hurt.
No, you're not.
You're safe.
You're here. I'm here.
We're safe. Everything's fine.
It's not, though.
You know, it was
a tough decision for me to make,
but it had to be done.
- You don't get it.
- Get what?
Let's go, Lion.
[Roars]
"Wow, Steven,
that was so brave of you.
I'm so glad you're back."
What?!
And Lars is still in space?!
Yeah, he is,
but don't worry,
he's with
some very nice gems
who are on the run
from their Homeworld overlords.
Oh, Laaaars.
Sadie, he's fine.
We can go see him anytime
through Lion.
Glad he's not ...  At least he's
some kind of alive.
You told his parents, right?
You're kind of
my practice run for that.
[Bell dings]
[Sighs]
Let's do this quick.
I can't be away from work
too long.
I'm basically
their only employee now.
[Shouting, booing]
Whoa, what's going on?
Man: We're sick of it!
Am I right about it?!
Aliens nearly abducted
the whole town.
And what did Mayor "Billiam"
Dewey do about it?
That is right.
Jack and squat!
[All shouting]
Steven, I'm going to
Lars's parents' house.
Okay, I'll catch up with you.
And that is why
you should vote for me,
your favorite Nanefua,
for mayor of Beach City!
[All cheering]
When I say "Do we want Dewey?"
you say "No."
- Do we want Dewey?
- All: No!
Nanefua: Okay, good job.
Hmm. "Can't hang today.
Mayor D's getting blamed
for Gem stuff,
and it's totally my fault."
I don't know, Universe.
This doesn't look good.
- How's this?
- Oh. That looks great.
But I may need more.
My gosh. I've never had
an opponent before.
Even when I ran for mayor
of high school, I ran unopposed.
Probably because
I made up the position.
If only
I could've warned you
about this abduction stuff
sooner,
then everything
would be fine now.
I really
dropped the ball.
You're right, Universe.
This is all your fault.
Huh.
How about we call
an impromptu town meeting
on the boardwalk?
I'll tell everyone what happened
and how you weren't
involved at all,
and everyone'll
feel better
and vote for you
in the next election.
All right, Universe.
The ball's
back in your court.
Just, uh...
don't drop it again, huh?
So, in conclusion, Mayor Dewey
had nothing whatsoever to do
with the abductions.
Everything was my fault
because I unknowingly provided
some space Gems
with a list of names
and put everyone in danger.
Mayor Dewey
would never do anything
to purposefully endanger
the town.
He basically
just keeps a low profile
and doesn't get involved
in much of anything.
Yeah, maybe
he should be involved!
He's the mayor!
[Crowd booing]
Thanks for listening,
and please vote for him
in the next Beach City
mayoral election.
Oh, ho, ho, yeah!
Hello, everyone.
Thanks for coming. Wow!
This whole abduction business
was a real close call, huh? Whoo.
But look around you.
Everyone is safe and accounted for.
That's not true!
What about my friend Lars?
Who?
What?
Lars! Lars Barriga?!
Mr. And Mrs. Barriga's son!
Did you even know
he was still missing?
Did you know he was
still somewhere in space?!
What kind of mayor doesn't
know when his own people
- are lost in space?!
- The donut boy?
Is that why the donut shop
was closed this morning?
- Yeah, but ...
- Do not worry.
I will do everything in my power
to hire a new donut boy.
[Crowd booing]
No!
You've got to be kidding me!
How did this get
on the Internet so fast?
I didn't invite any press to this event.
Someone posted it on Tube-Tube.
Only 12 people have seen it.
12 people?!
That's half the town!
I'm finished, Universe.
I don't know of many political figures
that have made a comeback
after getting a tomato to the face.
Oh, again, and again,
and again, and again.
You need to stop looping that.
Look, we're gonna
get through this together, okay?
Tomorrow is the big debate.
You still have one more chance
to win back the town's love.
But Steven, some of the
things people have been
saying about me are
really painful and mean.
We've just got to change
the conversation.
We can start with this.
"How to talk to people"?
I'm going to get you ready
for that debate,
even if it takes all night.
[Crowd murmuring]
All right.
[Yawns]
Today's the day.
You got your note cards,
you look great,
and if anyone brings up
the alien invasion thing,
I wrote a bunch of Ocean Town
jokes for you to use.
Aww, shucks, Universe.
You're like the son
I never had.
You...have a son.
I know that.
You're just very different
from him, is all.
[Crowd chanting "speech"]
[Whines]
I'm rooting for you,
Dew Drops.
[Weakly] Thanks.
[Chanting continues]
[Chanting stops]
[Clears throat]
[Microphone feedback]
People of Beach City.
You might think
that being a mayor is a fine
and glamorous
sort of thing.
I can understand why my opponent
would want the position.
But I've been mayor of this city
for a decade,
and I know some things
that Ms. Nanefua does not.
You see, when you're the mayor,
you get blamed for everything.
When the boardwalk has termites,
it's the mayor's fault.
When aliens steal people,
When the mayor crashes
the mayor mobile
into the only cell tower
in town, it's the mayor's fault.
Most people can't handle that
kind of pressure, but I can.
So, I say to you,
Beach City citizens,
just enjoy our wonderful ocean breeze
and don't worry about a thing.
Just let Dewey "do" it for you!
[Crowd murmuring,
applause]
Nice.
You know, Mayor Dewey,
you are right.
I am?
A-About what?
I have blamed you
for too many things,
and that is not helping.
[Crowd murmuring]
What?
Blaming our problems
completely on the mayor
is not getting us
anywhere.
When one of us suffers,
the town suffers.
When you suffer, Mayor Billiam,
So, no longer will I
point my fingers at you.
I will extend all my fingers
on both my hands
to everyone here today
and ask that we share
responsibility
for the welfare and safety
of Beach City, together!
Thank you.
[Cheers and applause]
[Chanting "Nanefua"]
You got this, Mayor Dewey.
[Stammering]
Uh, did you ever notice
how people from Ocean Town ...
Oh, who am I kidding?
Beach City deserves
a real mayor.
Someone wise and collected
like Ms. Nanefua.
[Crowd murmuring]
Wait.
No, no, no.
I withdraw
from the race.
You can find the key to the city
under the city welcome mat.
[Cheers and applause]
[Sighs]
Mayor Dewey,
what're you doing?!
Y-You can't just
throw the election like that.
W-We could still win!
Well, I know
it's not very traditional
to do that in the middle of
a debate, but why drag it out?
We could have won!
I-I really believed in you!
- I really believed in us!
- Well, you were wrong.
- What do you want me to say?
- How about, "I'm sorry.
We were in this together,
and I let you down."
Come on, Universe.
You know she's gonna be
a better mayor than me.
It was the right thing to do.
I guess, but... I still feel betrayed.
That's probably how Connie feels.
Yeah, I don't know
what you're talking about,
but I've got to find a new job.
[Humming]
[Tapping, phone dialing]
[Dialing continues]
[Music]
- Addi7ed.com -