- - Addic7ed.com - -
[Alarm beeping]
[Music]
[Barking]
Ooh. Hey there, girl.
Yo, Steven!
This a bad time?
Of the three things I have to do
in the sink now,
this is the one
I least mind you seeing.
Ugh, Peridot is still depressed
all up in your B-room?
Yeah. She still hasn't
gotten over Lapis leaving
and taking the barn
with her into space.
I think she just needs
a little more time to herself.
Nope, that's it,
we're getting her out.
Wait, Amethyst!
Uh, Peridot?
[Country music playing]
You... feeling any better?
Uugghhh.
[Music stops]
So, what have you been up to?
[Mumbling]
I, uh, couldn't really
hear you there.
[Groans]
Nothing.
You've been in this bathroom
kind of a long time.
Maybe you should
get some fresh air.
What's the point?
- To feel better?
- Come on, Peridot!
I can't stand seeing you
like this.
- Like what?
- Dude, let's just get out of the house.
We could go check out
my old kindergarten!
We met all those other Amethysts
up in space,
and they all came out of
the same rock as me.
I've been meaning to get a look
at the old neighborhood
now that I've met the neighbors.
That sounds fun.
What do you say, Peridot?
you can make us feel dumb
by telling us all the stuff
we don't know!
I miss that.
Great, it's settled!
Let's get out of the bathroom.
- Can I bring my music? [Whimpers]
- No.
[Music]
Ugh.
Why exactly are we taking
this outdated, clackity ship there?
The prime kindergarten has
a very convenient warp pad.
Eh, we're taking
the scenic route!
Come on, Peridot! Take a look
at the beautiful countryside.
No.
Your efforts to entrance me
with Earth's beauty
are pointless.
My sector of countryside
was perfect.
Now it's somewhere in space.
Just let me know
when we get there.
Good ol' kindergarten!
Just the way I left it!
Aw,
some things never change!
Gah, actually,
everything's different now!
Man, I-I used to think this
place was full of empty holes,
but now it's like
it's empty with holes
which were once full!
All those Amethysts
I met in space ...
they were all here!
While I was right there
in the ground.
But now I can finally start
putting some faces to holes!
Hohohoh, let's see...
Hup!
This must've been 8XJ!
Ooh!
8XK!
8XL!
Peridot: Actually, the order
goes from top to bottom.
- That's 8XJ.
- Really?
Yes. Curly hair, right?
Yeah! How'd you know?
You can tell from the iron
deposits in the formation there.
And that's 8XL down below.
Whoa, that's pretty amazing, Dot.
This used to make sense to me.
I thought life was generated
in a kindergarten.
Formless, aimless energy
channeled into new, useful gems.
But life doesn't start in a
kindergarten. It ends here.
I've gotten used to
plants everywhere.
Bugs and breeze and sunshine...
all of that has been
sucked out of this place.
It's with the Amethysts
that were produced here,
and now this place is
nothing but a miserable husk.
All of the Amethysts are gone.
Hey!
Oh, all the well-made
Amethysts are gone.
Yo, not better.
And nothing will ever
grow here again,
not even this flower.
Wait!
Oh!
I've never seen anything
growing here,
and I've been hanging around
this joint for 5,000 years.
Man,
it looks healthy, too.
Wow!
That's Earth for you ...
- always bouncing back.
- I don't know.
I'd have to run some tests
to see if this is not an anomaly.
You want to try planting stuff here?
You know how to farm!
Yeah, that could be fun!
It could be
an interesting experiment.
Yeah! Let's re-garden
the kindergarten!
[Zing!]
[Music]
[Gulls crying]
[Alarm beeping]
[Music]
Peridot: They don't need
any more water after yesterday,
- but according to...
- Ahh.
...several tutorials I read,
the roots should be
starting to take hold.
Oh, yeah?
So that's something we can check
for today, as soon as ... Steven!
What are you doing
in that bathing gown?!
Get dressed already!
Oh, uh, right.
[Train whistle blows]
Do you think
they grew much overnight?
Yeah, I bet the place
looks even better!
We should plant
even more stuff.
What do you think
we should do next?
- What about hydrangeas?
- Uh, which one's that?
I don't know,
but it sounds good, right?
What do you think, Peridot?
Hey, thanks for doing this with me.
- What? [Chuckles] Come on.
- It was fun.
I'm just glad
I was able to fix something.
Yeah, the kindergarten looks
better than ever!
[Wind whistling]
Well, I don't know
why I'm surprised.
I should've known
not to have hope.
But maybe if we try again...
It's not going to work!
It's never going to work, okay?!
Hey, don't be a jerk!
We were just trying to
cheer you up.
And good job with that!
I feel just great
now that I know
that nothing's ever
going to get better!
Everything is just
ruined forever!
We can't get
any of it back!
Not my home! Not Lapis!
And not this crummy planet,
either!
We might as well just
throw it all in the garbage
and toss ourselves in after,
because it's
all just hopeless trash!
Peridot, maybe the sunflowers
didn't work,
but we know
something can grow here.
This clod's just like us!
Too dumb
to get with the program!
[Squish!]
[Whimpers]
[Rumbling]
Uhhh.
- Uh?
- Waaaa!
[Crack!]
[Roars]
Oh, of course!
Peridot!
[Roars]
Whoa!
[Panting]
- Want to get this together?
- Let's do it!
[Music]
[Roaring]
I need to
go to the bathroom.
Man, you were right.
The kindergarten really is
dead forever.
I was a fool to think we could
reinstitute life there.
[Sighs]
Tell me about it.
All right. I will.
I was pretty much using this
as a distraction
from losing Lapis,
losing the barn,
and just a general sense of
complete hopelessness
I tend to deal with
on a day-to-day basis.
But it really only
confirmed for me
that once you mess something up,
it's ruined for good
and nothing will ever
be able to grow again.
Yeah, we got the subtext.
Oh, wow.
What about all this?
Now that's some plants.
Huh.
Guess the countryside out here
is pretty beautiful.
But who cares? I wanted to
have this for the kindergarten!
Even if there was nothing we can
do for that one patch of land,
there's still a whole Earth
blooming all around us.
Yeah!
Why don't we try gardening
in literally any other place?
It'll be easier than trying to
plant in the kindergarten.
That dirt doesn't care
how green your thumb is.
Green thumb!
'Cause you're green. [Laughs]
- I know that!
- So, are ya in?
- Um...
- Do it, do it, do it, say yes!
Ugh. Fine. I've got literally
nothing else to do.
- Oh, yeah!
- Yay!
[Music]
- - Addic7ed.com - -