- Garnet: # We #
- # Are the Crystal #
- Steven: # Gems #
- # we'll always save the day #
Steven: # and if you think we can't #
All: # we'll always find a way #
- # that's why the people #
- # of this world #
Garnet: # believe in... Garnet #
- # Amethyst #
- # and Pearl #
Steven: # And Steven! #
- - Addic7ed.com - -
[Waves crashing,
gulls squawking in distance]
[Sighs]
She'll call when she's ready.
For now, you just
have to let go.
[Squawking continues]
[Sighs]
♪ I wish I could
tell you that I ... ♪
Aah, aah!
[Cellphone buzzing]
Ah! Ah! Ugh!
Okay, Universe. This is it!
Connie's finally ready to talk.
No expectations.
Just let her say
what she needs to say!
Aw.
Peridot: Steven!
[Chuckles]
It's us.
Oh, hi, Peridot.
Hi, Lapis.
Don't forget Pumpkin!
[Barks]
[Chuckles]
Hi, Pumpkin!
I'd told you he'd answer.
It's so good to see you.
I'm glad you're okay.
Lapis was worried you lost
your phone on Homeworld,
but I said, "No way!
He's probably
just ignoring us."
Sorry, guys.
There's been... a lot going on.
- Like what? Tell us!
- Well, Connie is really mad at me.
No, no, no, no.
Tell us about space!
- And start from the beginning.
- Uh, okay.
I was trying to protect Beach City,
so I surrendered myself
to Homeworld,
and I was put in
a big, empty room,
and I ended up on trial
in front of the Diamonds!
- On trial?
- What?
- In front of the Diamonds?
- Yeah, and...
You were in front
of Blue Diamond?
And Yellow! But it's okay.
I escaped in a palanquin
and went underground and...
You ran from Blue
and Yellow Diamond?!
- Yes.
- Peridot, we have to leave Earth now.
[Sighing] Uh-oh.
[Pumpkin barking]
Wait. We can't leave.
- What about all our crops?
- Guys?
Ugh. The vegetables
will have to deal.
Okay. Okay, but, uh...
we're only halfway through our
rewatch of "CPH" season four.
[Chuckles] We'll bring
the box set with us.
But how are we going to
watch it without the TV?
We'll bring the TV.
- Uh, Lapis?
- Huh?
- Peridot?
- Oh, Steven. Good. Let's go.
- Wait. What?
- We'll find some remote spot
in the universe to hide out in.
The Diamonds will never find us.
Lapis, don't worry.
They're looking for me
on Homeworld.
They don't know I'm here.
We're safe.
Yeah. Come on.
We've gotten away with worse.
They've never been
able to hunt me down
- for my many crimes against them.
- This is different.
Steven is important, and our
transgressions are piling up!
They're going to take their
anger out on this planet,
just like they did before.
I can't.
I won't let myself get
caught up in another war.
[Whimpers]
I don't want you to leave,
but I won't ask you guys to stay
if you don't feel safe.
If you have to go,
I understand.
Right.
Peridot, if you want the TV,
levitate it over here.
Hey, um, what about our
meep morps we've made?
We can't leave them behind.
We can bring them, too.
But they're installations!
They need the context
of the barn!
If ... if we move them,
they'll become...
performance pieces.
There's no need
to get so emotional!
You're right. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Performance art isn't bad,
just misunderstood.
Hmm, maybe I can
do something.
Ah!
Our smaller-than-average lake!
Guh!
[Pumpkin barking]
- Whoa.
[Rumbling]
There. Now we can bring
our whole life with us ...
you, me, and all of our things.
- Right. Right!
- Well, let's get going.
You're leaving right now?
I thought that...
I ... I don't know what to say.
Goodbye, Steven.
Good luck. [Sniffles]
Peridot, don't you
want to say bye?
Uhh...
[Whimpers]
Umm...
[Gasps] Wait.
Where's Pumpkin?
- She's not inside?
- She was just standing next to me!
We have to find her.
I'll check from above.
Peridot, you search the ground.
- I'll help, too! Pumpkin?
- Pumpkin?!
Pumpkin? Pumpkin!
- Pumpkin? Pumpkin!
- Pumpkin?
[Softly] Pumpkin.
Pumpkin!
Where are you, buddy?
[Panting]
Pumpkin!
[Music]
You know, I'm really
going to miss you guys
when you're in space.
Well, that's a given.
I'm a very precious Gem.
Without me,
you would have crumbled
under The Cluster's
obstructive force
or have been smushed
by Jasper.
I'm ...
Peridot, there!
Pumpkin! Ngh!
Is she okay?
Um...
Pumpkin!
You know, I can
probably still help you
when I'm out in space.
I'll just video chat
from my tablet.
Uh, t-there's no Wi-Fi in space.
Well, maybe it's best
if we can't reach you.
If the Diamonds do show up
and destroy the planet,
we'll never know!
Lapis was very agitated when
she heard you were on Homeworld.
I was bending over backwards
to make her feel better.
Watch this.
[Grunting]
[Laughs] That is good.
Oh, yeah.
She loves this.
[Groans]
Maybe it's good
that we'll be away
from everything
where nothing can change,
no surprises or developments.
She's been through so much.
- She needs consistency.
- But what about you?
[Gasps]
Another kindergartner!
Fresh produce?
Pumpkin is fresh produce!
[Both panting]
It's just onions?
Pumpkin would never associate
with this inferior sphere.
- Aah!
Uh, Onion?
What are you ...
Hey, is that my hat?
Well, that was a bust.
- We'll never find Pumpkin.
- Peridot... [Rustling]
Pumpkin?
[Whimpers]
Have you been here
the whole time?!
- She was hiding?
- Come on, Pumpkin.
We need to leave.
[Whimpers]
Pumpkin!
Don't you walk away
while I'm talking to you.
[Whimpers, barking]
[Grunting]
Sometimes, you have to do things
you don't want to do,
like get jettisoned into
space to live forever
on a floating rock
with a barn,
and just us for as long
as time exists!
Lapis needs us!
Peridot, give her a second.
She's doing it to herself!
Pumpkin, do as you're told!
Aah!
[Whimpers]
Whoa, Peridot.
It sounds like you
don't really want to go.
I'm sorry, Pumpkin.
I didn't mean
to yank you around.
It's just we don't have
a choice in this.
What do you mean,
you don't have a choice?
Peridot, you should really
talk to Lapis about this.
- I can't.
- What? Why not?
Oh, great.
You found her!
Now, let's go.
[Rumbling]
[Music]
[Shivering]
[Shivers]
Wait... Lapis?
Pumpkin doesn't want to go.
Pumpkin doesn't know better.
We do.
Actually, I...
I don't want to go either.
What?!
- Aah!
Ooh-whoa!
[Yelps]
Peridot, what are you
trying to say?
It's just, if something
happens on Earth,
- I want to be here for it!
- But ... no!
Why are you telling me this now?!
Because we're about to leave!
- Isn't that the worst time?
- Yes.
[Chuckles nervously]
Then why didn't
you tell me sooner?
Well, there are many
things I should say,
but they would upset you,
so in general,
I don't say those things.
Peridot, that's lying!
[Groaning]
Okay, then! The truth is...
I think that we should stay,
and if ... and if the time comes,
if the Diamonds do come to wipe
this planet off the star maps,
I think we should fight
for this life we've built
instead of tearing it up
out of the ground!
I think we can win.
I think you can win.
Earth is our home now.
Isn't it worth fighting for?
What do you say, Lapis?
[Music]
I am not getting caught in
the middle of another war.
[Rumbling]
Wait! No!
You're supposed to
reward me
for my emotional honesty!
[Sighs]
[Insects chirping]
Come on. Let's go.
Okay.
You're all set up,
and you can stay here
as long as you need.
Wow. [Groans]
Thanks.
[Sighs]
What do we do now?
- - Addic7ed.com - -