- Addic7ed.com -
"Hey, Connie.
How are you today?
Hope everything's going okay.
It'd be cool if you told me it was...
I guess I miss you.
I know yesterday I said,
'I guess,' but I mean,
I do miss you...
Hope you didn't get your phone
mixed up with a tennis ball.
Ha ha."
A tennis ball?
Really, Universe?
Help! Ah! Yah!
Back!
Ugh!
Hey, uh, Stevearoni, ugh,
want to help
your old Pa over here?
Uh, yeah, Dad, one sec.
Sorry. Sorry.
I'm on it.
Are you good? Are you safe?
Do you still love me?
Yeah, of ...
of course, buddy.
It's just some hoses.
I can buy new ones.
I still have like
$9 million left,
and what better way
to spend that
than on some hoses,
right, kiddo?
Yeah, Dad.
Steven!
So. Did you ever get around to
watching the "Koala Princess"
box set I lent you three months ago?
Hey, is everything okay?
You're looking a little glum.
- I am a little glum.
- Do you want to talk about it?
Um, it's just space lag
from when I went to space.
Hmm.
Ah!
Wait. No.
I need to play it cool.
I'm just gonna assume by your silence
that you're entangled within
the immersive koala lore
of the show.
Did you get to the part
where Koala Princess
and Kanga-Roofus kiss?
Steven, you want to help
us with these groceries?
Coming.
Eh? Eh?
Check this out, Steven.
It's farm fresh.
Uh, thanks guys,
but the fridge is full.
Not the fridge
at our vacation house.
- Whoo!
- Vacation.
I thought,
"Why spend money on hoses
when I can spend it
on houses?"
So I found a place
we could rent
for the weekend
by searching online.
Back in the old days
we just went door-to-door
hoping one was unlocked,
but this is the new days.
Okay. Well, have fun.
Uh, Steven, you're going
on vacation, too.
Oh, yes. This is the
perfect time for a vacation.
I mean, how often are we
on the same planet together?
Yeah. And you'll be
with your favorite Gems
and your favorite dad.
Agree with Amethyst.
Turn to Steven.
Steven, you should go.
No, with more enthusiasm.
Steven, it's a vacation!
I mean, I would,
but I'm really tied up
with something important.
In the end,
the wombats were for naught,
but it really makes you think.
I'll go.
Aced it.
Here it is, temporary
home sweet temporary home.
- Is that my bed?
- Yeah.
I want you to be
a comfortable as possible,
finally have
some family time.
I feel like you haven't
had that in a while.
Yeah, maybe.
This place is great.
They have one
of those refrigerators
that dispense water,
not to mention four windows
and an analog clock!
Hmm, says here
we can't use
the water dispenser
or the clock.
Windows must be kept
closed at all times,
and remove all shoes
before entering.
Hmm.
Hey, Greg, did you invite
anyone else, party guy,
about three feet long,
hissing, reptilian?
No.
Well, you might want
to factor in a plus one.
- Oh! Party guy, no!
- I promise.
It's gonna be
a really good time.
It's a great place, Dad.
It only bit Pearl once,
but, like, we're Gems.
She'll be okay.
It isn't the pain.
It's the surprise.
Hey, Amethyst, do you think
you could...
Yeah.
Hey, Steven.
Hi, Amethyst.
Man, you can see the stars
so clearly out here.
It's pretty, huh?
Huh?
Uh, I don't know.
- It's okay.
- Hey, hey.
It's okay if it isn't okay.
- The sky?
- Yeah.
- What?
- I don't know.
So, uh, you really
into phones now?
No.
Hey, Schtuball,
won't you take my place?
I've been in here way too long.
I'm gonna become a raisin.
Steven,
you should join me.
Become a raisin.
Okay, but one sec.
Steven, I know
what's troubling you.
You do?
Gosh.
I really messed up, didn't I?
You didn't do
anything wrong.
Pink Diamond
was a villain.
It was 5,750 years ago.
Pink Diamond was
ravishing the planet.
- Yeah, I know.
- Oh.
Pink Diamond was bad.
Everything bad
had to happen
so good things
could kind of happen.
Uh, good.
You understand.
Buzz.
At least wiggle a little.
Come on. Can't you
give it another shot?
What are we supposed to do?
He just doesn't want
to talk about it.
But I know
it's not space lag.
This is some Gem thing
he knows I won't understand.
I don't know anything
about Homeworld.
about your society.
Whatever horrible things
he saw out there,
you guys have to
put it into context.
If Steven won't
talk to us,
then the help we can
give him is limited.
We've all tried
to coax it out of him
except for...
Me?
But I have no idea
what Homeworld is like now.
Pearl, please.
He knows you know
about space stuff.
It can't hurt to try.
Mm.
Huh. It sure is quiet
out here, huh?
- Yeah.
- So, Homeworld...
I always hoped
you'd see it some day,
but I thought
I'd be there with you.
Being taken there
as a prisoner,
I suppose it was something
of a dramatic experience.
It's just, Steven,
I'm sure you have
a lot of questions
you'd like answers to,
like about the Diamonds,
for instance.
There are things that are
impossible for me to explain.
But I want to.
I ...
Steven, I ...
Connie hates me!
What?
We weren't listening.
Also continue, Steven.
I'm not upset about
what happened on Homeworld
although, yeah, a lot of that
was really messed up.
But my relationship with Connie
is even more messed up.
I left her behind
to go to Homeworld
after promising we'd face
everything together.
I'm sure I really hurt her.
I've been calling
and texting her for a week,
but she hasn't
responded once.
Connie might never
talk to me again.
Steven!
I'll go get him.
I don't know anything
about Homeworld,
but I know about this.
Steven?
Steven's not here.
Oh, that's too bad.
So I guess I'll just
talk to this
Steven-shaped barrel
instead.
If you must.
Schtuball, if this was
about Connie,
why didn't you say
anything sooner?
I was embarra...
You were embroidered,
embroiled,
emboldened to talk
to your old man
about your problems?
I was embarrassed,
okay?
You and the Gems
all liked Connie,
and I was worried that if you
heard what happened
that you'd be
mad at me too.
Oh, Steven, of course
we're not mad.
And I'm sure
Connie's not mad, either.
Well, at least I'm sure
she doesn't hate you.
That whole handing-yourself
over-to-Homeworld thing
was definitely
a high-stress situation.
It really scared
all of us.
I'm not exactly
over it either,
but I guess
carting you off
to the middle of nowhere
to spend time with you
is my way
of dealing with it.
Maybe having some distance
from you is Connie's way.
But the last thing I did was
send her a bunch of dumb texts.
I made some weird joke
about tennis,
and I don't even know
if it makes sense.
- Tennis?
- See?
No wonder she hasn't responded.
Uh, Steven, you don't
get any service out here.
Whaaaat are you even telling me?
Maybe she's been
trying to get in touch
with me this whole time,
and I haven't seen it!
What if she thinks I'm ignoring her?
Dad!
We have to find cell service.
Right.
- Go, go, go!
- Okay.
Floor it!
- How we doing?
- Take a right.
Nah, back up.
No, wait!
Keep going.
- We're heading for a cliff, buddy.
- Just a little further.
- Gonna have to stop soon.
- Almost got it.
Ahh!
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Yes!
We've got service.
Steven! When I didn't
hear back from you,
I was sure a nefarious plot
was afoot...
Well?
No. No messages from Connie.
Aw. You'll get
through this, buddy.
I know it hurts now,
but give it time.
I know.
I need to let it go.
- Got room for three more?
- Always.
- Nice night, isn't it?
- Yeah.
- Addic7ed.com -