- Garnet: # We #
- # Are the Crystal #
- Steven: # Gems #
- # we'll always save the day #
Steven: # and if you think we can't #
All: # we'll always find a way #
- # that's why the people #
- # of this world #
Garnet: # believe in...
Garnet #
- # Amethyst #
- # and Pearl #
Steven: # And Steven! #
~ Addic7ed.com ~
[Grunts]
Lars, are you okay?
Thanks to your bubble...
[groans]
my bones are
only a little broken.
[Chuckles]
My bones, too.
[Groans]
Dude, those giant ladies
were furious with you.
They're the diamonds.
They've been after my mom
for 6,000 years,
and now they're after me.
Come on.
We got to move.
How are we supposed
to get off this planet?
Do you even know
where you're going?
No. This is my
first time here, too.
[Groans]
This is so messed up.
What are we gonna eat?
There's tons of food
if you like rocks for dinner.
Salt is a rock, right?
Maybe we can season some dirt
and make a meal.
Wait!
[Low rumbling]
Uh...
Sorry.
[Both gasp]
They found us!
- Run!
- Wait!
If we stand perfectly still,
it won't see us!
I saw it
in a movie once.
That sounds good.
Uh...
We should probably move!
- Aah!
I think that movie
was about dinosaurs.
Lars, come on!
Whoa!
[Music]
What are we gonna do?
What's gonna happen?
We're gonna run,
and we're gonna be okay!
No!
You just don't get it!
I hate being scared
all the time!
I was scared of everything
except baking.
Actually,
I was scared of that, too.
I never even tried
making baklava
'cause it looked
so hard!
I never had the guts
to stick up for anybody...
not even me!
And now I'm hiding again
like a big cowardly loser
under some
space building!
Don't beat yourself up
like that, Lars.
That's what the killer robots
are for.
- Quickly!
- Down here!
Steven!
What if it's a trap?
Uh...
I don't think we have a choice!
Aah!
[Both sigh]
Close one, huh?
Yeah, but who ...
Rutile Right: Don't worry.
You're safe now.
We're not gonna hurt you.
Thank you,
whoever you...
[Screams]
[Both gasp]
It's okay, Lars.
Thank you for saving us.
How bizarre.
What are they?
They certainly don't look like
gems we've ever seen before.
Come, this way!
This way, come!
Steven, wait.
Is this really a good idea?
They seem...different.
I think we can trust them.
[Music]
Uh, excuse me, but, um,
where are you taking us?
Somewhere long forgotten.
Where only those
who don't belong belong.
[Chuckles]
Sounds like my kind of place.
You don't happen to have
any fast-food joints
around there, do you?
Whoa!
What is this place?
[Echoing]
A kindergarten.
A really, really big one.
[Both whistle]
We're back!
Here we are!
It's okay to come out!
Oh, thank goodness.
I hope you weren't followed.
You weren't, right?
You double-checked?
[Gasps]
You've been followed!
Uh, hi!
Uh, don't worry.
I'm not a threat or anything.
Rutile Left: It's okay, Rhodonite.
Relax.
We brought them here.
They're with us.
Can we trust them?
- Sure.
- I think so.
- Everyone!
- Huh?
A wondrous vision has appeared
before me.
The twins of rutile
will bring one ... no, two ...
strangers to our current
place of hiding.
We know, Padparadscha.
Your prediction
already happened.
They were being chased up
on the surface
by one of those
terrible robonoids.
Don't tell me you tried to fight
those things.
No, no.
Of course not.
These two
were about to be scanned
when we pulled them under.
We were just in time.
Fluorite: Let me see.
[Lars screams]
Uh...
Aah!
They don't look
like Gems.
That's what I said!
I said the same thing!
Hi! I'm Steven.
I'm a Gem.
Well, half-gem.
And this is Lars.
He's all human.
That's why you look
so unusual.
We look unusual?!
Of course you do!
You can't just walk around
on the surface like that!
You're off-color ...
just like the rest of us!
What do you mean,
off-color?
You know, wrong.
Not, right.
Flawed.
Wait, I don't see anything wrong
with you guys.
Gems like us aren't needed.
Padparadscha can only predict
things that just happened.
Here comes Fluorite!
And a fusion like me
is unforgivable.
When my ...
our Morganite found out,
let's just say
we were replaced.
But my story's nothing!
I mean, Fluorite,
how many Gems are you now?
Six.
Maybe more,
if we meet the right Gem.
And then there's us!
You mean, you're not a fusion?
We're just a rutile
that came out wrong.
We survived
because all the other rutiles
ran away when we emerged.
We survived because
they were afraid of us.
Afraid of you?
So you've been hiding
your whole lives.
- What happens if they find you?
- We'll be...
Shattered.
[Low rumbling]
- Oh.
- No!
Oh.
[Whimpers]
Ah! You were followed!
They're gonna find us!
They're gonna break us!
This is our fault!
If it wasn't for us, you'd be fine!
We couldn't
just leave you there.
We had to do something.
Steven?
What're we gonna do?
Everyone hide!
Careful, everyone!
We're about to be found!
[Music]
Lars...
It's okay to be afraid.
Okay.
[Gasps]
Oh, no!
- We got to do something!
- Lars!
[Music]
- [Gasps] Lars!
- It's okay to be afraid.
[Sighs]
Oh, my gosh! Lars!
They were trying to scan
your Gem!
They can't see you
at all!
All right!
Looks like the tables
have turned!
- Human Lars.
- [Gasps]
I've been possessed
by the most marvelous vision!
Huh?
You, human Lars,
are Gemless,
and will be safe
from the robonoids,
which only target Gems!
I think that's the coolest thing
I've ever done in my life.
It's not over yet.
[Grunts]
Huh?
Oh.
The shield is reflective.
Padparadscha, come back!
Hide!
Okay.
Okay!
Whoa-oh-oh!
Whoa! Aah!
Whoa!
Eat this!
Lars!
Lars?
I didn't think
we were gonna make it!
- That was amazing!
- Lars, that was so great.
- You were amazing.
- We're winning!
We're winning!
[Gasps]
[Crying]
[Groans]
Whoa.
What happened?
Oh, my!
Something incredible
is going to happen to Lars!
~ Addic7ed.com ~