Translated By The Community Of WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
- # We
- Are the Crystal #
- # Gems
- We'll always save the day #
♪ And if you think we can't ♪
♪ We'll always find a way ♪
- # That's why the people
- Of this world #
♪ Believe in... Garnet ♪
- # Amethyst
- And Pearl #
♪ And Steven! ♪
- MY-SUBS.com -
If you see him,
call me right away.
He's my only inter-dimensional
gateway to space,
and I love him.
Okay, I think I have
enough fliers left to ...
What are you doing
Saturday night?
- Hey! Listen! Little kid!
- Beat it, Kevin.
I'm throwing a party
at my parents' palatial estate.
All the coolest teens
in Delmarva have RSVP'd
except one ...
the only one cooler than I am.
Are you talking about me?
What? No! Ew!
- I'm talking about Stevonnie.
- W-What?!
You can't just ...
This is the last thing
I need right now.
Look, Stevonnie is better
than me, okay?
Better dancer, better driver.
Stevonnie truly does not care
what anyone thinks.
That's why they're the coolest.
If I can't be the coolest,
I at least got to be seen
hanging with the coolest.
Stevonnie only exists
when Connie and I are together,
and we're...
I'm not coming.
Great.
So I invited that other kid
for nothing.
Wh... Connie's going?!
Of course she's going.
No one turns down an
invitation to a Kevin party.
But she can't stand you.
Why would she ...
Wait.
Did you say
all of this to her, too?
Does she think I'm ...
I'm gonna be there?
- Is it too late to RSVP?
- Yes.
But I'll make an exception...
for Stevonnie.
Wait. What's your number?
I'll text you the address.
Oh. Yeah, uh, 301-555...
Here, you enter it.
Okay, uh, how do I...?
You roll the little ball to navigate.
The screen is so tiny.
Here.
Huh, your name's Steven?
Weird.
I thought it was Clarence.
See you at the party Saturday, Steven.
Steven!
What took you so long?!
I-I got lost
coming up the driveway.
Yo, Kev, who invited
the 7-year-old, bro?
Hey, shut your mouth,
Derrick!
I thought I told you
to go buy more ice!
Ugh. You just come from picture
day at school or something?
I brought snacks?
Wha...?
This party is lame enough
as it is.
Look at these people.
This is forgettable.
But not for long.
Every time Stevonnie shows up
on the scene,
everybody's
talking about it.
And when Stevonnie shows up
at my party,
everyone's gonna be
talking about this night
until they're
old grandparents,
and their last words
to their grandchildren will be,
"Kevin throws the best parties."
Um...
Lion?!
Wait, you're the one
who had him the whole time?!
What? Ugh!
No, I'm allergic to dogs.
Then what's he doing here?
- Connie!
- Hey!
I haven't seen her in so long.
She looks so different.
Ugh!
I thought she'd be here
to see me,
but maybe she's just here
to have a good time.
Maybe she's moved on.
She's moved on?
Wait,
did you guys break up?
Can 7-year-olds
even do that?
I'm 14.
You didn't tell me
you guys broke up.
You got a free ticket
to what would have been
the best teen party
in Delmarva.
But now it's just
some sad kid party
getting crashed
by a couple of sad kids!
All right, okay.
I'm ... I'm leaving.
No.
When did this happen?
A few weeks ago.
Hmm.
You been texting her?
Several dozen times.
She text you back?
Um, no.
Hmm, but she knew
you'd be here.
Right! Right.
I'll ... I'll just go
talk to her.
I'll ...
I'll just go tell her
how sorry I am.
I-I really messed up.
I-I was an idiot!
And I ...
Whoa! No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, kid, listen.
I wouldn't normally do this
because you're a pitiful kid
with snot coming out
of your nose...
...but I need
those old people
to whisper my name
when they die.
And if you don't
pull it together,
you're gonna regret it.
And it'll be Sabina
all over again!
Wh... Who's...
Who's Sabina?
You can't just dump
your emotional honesty face
all over her.
You're gonna freak her out.
I-I just want us to talk again.
Exactly.
But look what she's doing.
Life is good.
She's got a dog now.
And a haircut.
Right.
But your life is good, too.
You don't need
to talk to her, either.
You've got new stuff going on ...
new friends, new shirt.
She gave this to me
for my birthday.
Ugh.
Derrick!
Gimme your jacket.
What? No.
Dude!
- Derrick! Give me the ...
- Come on!
Here. Put this on.
Your friend looks
kind of mad, though.
He's not my friend.
Put it on. Collar up.
Hmm, not quite
cool enough.
I got it.
Nice.
It's almost like
you have style.
Why do I need the scarf?
It's not even cold out.
When you put on a scarf
like this, it's always cool.
Let's show her
what a great time you're having.
Hey, kid,
you should say hi to Connie.
So I can tell her
about my feelings?
No. Be casual.
You're showing her
how you have it together.
You're not dying
to talk to her
because you're not dying
at all.
You're living.
Make her want
that life with you.
Kevin, that ...
that's kind of moving.
So move already.
Walk over, be cool,
and walk away.
Got it.
Okay. Be cool.
Be cool, yeah. Be cool.
- Hey!
- Hi.
Nice weather
you're wearing.
- Uh, I got your texts.
- Oh, yeah.
I forgot about those
because I've been living.
Wha...?
Well,
back to my great life.
Uh, chowzers.
That was terrible!
This is all wrong,
Kevin!
No way.
Look, little man.
Your girl's making her way
back for more.
Steven!
What is going on?!
I came here
hoping we could talk,
but it seems like you only want
to talk to Kevin.
I guess Kevin is your best friend now.
- What? No, no, no!
Anyway,
I'm glad you're doing well.
That's all I really wanted to know.
No, no! But ...
But you're my best friend!
Best friend?! What are you kids
even talking about?
I thought she was your ex.
Great.
Now what am I gonna do?
Think, Kevin.
How do people treat their friends?
Connie!
Wait, wait, Connie.
Don't go.
Steven, I wasn't trying
to ignore you.
I was going to text you back.
I-I wrote,
"I can't talk to you right now,"
but then I realized if I sent it,
that would be talking to you.
And it didn't make any sense.
I wasn't making any sense.
If we were
going to talk,
I thought it's got to be in person.
So I rode Lion to your house,
but there was a note that said,
"Gone vacationing,"
and then I ran into Kevin
and he said you'd be here,
but, uh, maybe this is still too soon.
I-I don't even know
what to say to you.
I'm angry.
I miss you.
I feel like
I'm out of my mind.
No, you're not.
I surrendered myself
to Homeworld.
I let them take me away,
maybe forever,
and then I came back and I tried
to act like it was no big deal.
But it was a big deal.
I couldn't stand
the thought
of you being taken away
on that spaceship,
but then I did that to you.
I promised you we'd always be
a team, and I let you down.
I'm sorry.
Jam buds?
Jam buds.
It's so good to talk to you.
I've been wanting to see you
so bad
I accepted a party invitation
from Kevin.
I know. I took his advice.
I think he got is heart broken.
I-It's actually really sad.
Of course he did.
- Hey, nice shirt.
- Nice hair.
Thank you.
All right!
Hey, everybody, are you having fun?
Yeah!
Liars!
You're all so fake.
You make me sick.
But get ready.
I'm gonna introduce you
to somebody so real
you'll all feel as sick as me!
This party starts now!
Children! Go!
It's pretty late.
We should head out.
Thanks for all your help, Kevin.
What?
You got to do the thing.
What did I help you for if
you're not gonna elevate my party?
Wha...? Hey!
Don't you walk away from...
Shut up, Derrick!
If it helps, Kevin, I think
you threw a very nice party.
Mm-hmm.
Good night!
No! Wait!
- MY-SUBS.com -