- Garnet: # We #
- # Are the Crystal #
- Steven: # Gems #
- # we'll always save the day #
Steven: # and if you think we can't #
All: # we'll always find a way #
- # that's why the people #
- # of this world #
Garnet: # believe in... Garnet #
- # Amethyst #
- # and Pearl #
Steven: # And Steven! #
- - Addic7ed.com - -
Steven: Good old Beach City,
but so much has changed lately.
I guess after
all those abductions,
everything couldn't
just return to normal.
With Sadie rocking out
and Lars in space,
I can't even enjoy
my regular snack at
the Big Donut.
What am I gonna do
for breakfast now?!
[Groans]
[Grunts]
[Doorbell rings]
Wait a minute.
Big Donut is still open?
[Gasps]
Hello.
Welcome to the Big Donut.
Garnet?
I have so many questions.
Just one moment.
You'll have to wait
your turn.
[Soft music plays]
[Ka-ching!]
[Doorbell rings]
Welcome to the Big Donut.
Tell me how I may serve you.
I never thought
I'd see you working here.
- Have we fallen on hard times?
- Oh, Steven.
This isn't about
making ends meet.
This is about being random.
Are you serious?
Oh, yes.
I...don't understand.
[Music]
My future vision allows me
to see down the rivers
of possibility,
granting me insight
into the possible realities
our actions move us towards.
But that doesn't mean
I can predict everything.
What I'm interested in
are these extremely
unlikely realities,
so disconnected from
the natural course of events
that I can't detect them.
When we act
in unnatural ways,
we create
new, unforeseen paths,
and arrive at these pools
of improbability.
Oh, so you want to do stuff
you usually don't
just to see what happens?
I didn't foresee
you understanding that.
So, are we gonna
clean up that coffee?
That's what
we'd normally do.
Let's see what happens
to the world
when we don't.
[Music]
[Coffee drips]
We are now dwelling
in a totally new pool
of improbability.
My future vision
is useless here.
I'm scared...
but intrigued.
That's the spirit!
Let's get
even more intriguing!
I quit!
Come, Steven!
[Soft music plays]
- So, what now?
- Hmm...
Instead of selling food,
let's order some.
Like what?
Let's do...pizza.
Now you're talking
my language!
Ordering now.
[Phone ringing]
Fish Stew Pizza.
Uh, I want to order a pizza.
- 10 pizzas!
- No, 20 pizzas!
Toppings?
Um...
- Surprise me.
- Now you're getting it!
I guess deliver it
to the Temple.
No...
That's just what
they'll be expecting.
Go weirder!
Deliver it to the ocean.
No, no, no!
To Kansas!
No, to the moon!
I don't think that's
within our delivery radius.
Remember.
Improbable, not impossible.
Where's the last place
they'd expect
to deliver a pizza?
Oh! Deliver it to...
Fish Stew Pizza.
So, like, this is for pick-up?
Now think, Steven,
about what you typically do
when you obtain pizza.
Hmm...
Eat it?
In this timeline,
we do the opposite of that.
Hey, you!
Have a pizza!
[Grunts]
Hey, thanks!
[Music]
[Seagulls squawking]
One more pizza
to deliver.
Hey, Vidalia's house
is around here.
Let's bring her
the last pie.
Now, that would be nice.
She must be upset
that her son
was taken into space
by those Homeworld gems.
You mean Onion?
He isn't in space.
He's right over there.
Sorry, I ... I must be thinking
of a different timeline.
Okay...
Well, I'm sure Vidalia
would still like some pizza
even if her kid
is still on Earth.
Let's go swing by.
[Knock on door]
Mother Onion! Open up!
Vidalia: In the garage!
[Music]
Get excited for pizza!
We got pepper flakes,
and we're not afraid
to use 'em!
Ahh! Wait a minute.
Steven?
What are you guys
doing here?
Trying to scare me
to death?
Oh, sorry.
We were just trying
to bring you a pizza
in the most unlikely way
possible.
Want a slice?
Sure,
I could use a break.
I've been working on
this still life
of a stepstool,
but I just don't feel
inspired.
[Music]
Paint me
like one of your Amethysts.
Paint me, too!
So you wanna be my muse,
eh?
If it's not
too much trouble.
I promise to be
very inspiring.
Hmm...
Yeah, I think this is just
what I needed.
Strike a pose!
It's struck.
Okay, don't move.
I need to capture
your essence.
[Music]
[Groaning]
Garnet?
How long do you see me
holding still?
Who knows?
The odds of us being here
are so slim,
I can't even ...
[Clanging in distance]
Uh, Garnet?
[Music]
Steven, look.
Ba-ba-b-b...
baby kitten?
Is it possible
that we chase that sweet cat?
It ... it's up to you,
Steven.
Yes?
Don't ask me.
Tell me.
Yes!
- Whoa!
- Huh?
[Music]
Sorry, Vidalia!
Maybe next time!
But wait!
Your essence!
[Music]
That's one fast kitten.
You think
we can catch it?
If we don't
lose sight of it.
[Music]
[Kittens meowing]
Steven: Aww...
There's more of them.
[Meowing continues]
Aww,
and they have no food.
Aww, and they have no one
to take care of them!
Garnet, we got to help
these kittens.
Look at you!
You're just babies.
Who knows what would've
happened to them
if we didn't find them?
Everything's gonna be
just fine.
We've got you.
[Meowing continues]
Here's the last one.
Or ... wait.
All right.
I think we got to stop
being random
and figure out what we can do
for these kittens.
Garnet, can you use
your future vision?
What should we do next?
Garnet?
There's so many...cats.
So many possibilities.
It's too much?
Okay,
can you focus on one?
What's this one's future?
I...
I don't know!
I don't know anything
anymore!
[Thunder rumbling]
Are you okay?
Steven, lately,
I've felt so lost.
Don't worry.
I remember the way
back to town.
Oh, it's not just that.
It's you.
You've made so many decisions
I didn't expect ...
giving yourself
up to Homeworld,
coming back
through Lion's mane.
The future that you created
was so improbable
that I didn't see it
coming at all,
and now I can't understand
where this timeline is going.
We're on the outskirts
of the possible,
following trickles
to who knows where.
Everyone's looking to me
for answers.
I can't stand it!
It's so hard for me
to just exist
in the first place,
Steven.
I want to love
being alive.
I want to love that there are
so many possibilities,
but I'm the one
with this ability,
so I've got to be our guide.
I thought, if I could use
my future vision
to jump into improbable futures,
I could get out ahead of
the next big, unexpected change,
but I don't know
what I'm doing here!
I can't tell
what's probable anymore!
Anything could happen!
Anything could happen
to these cats!
[Kittens meowing]
That's true,
but maybe instead of
thinking of all the things
that could happen,
let's just pick the thing
we want to happen
and do that.
So, what do you want
to happen next?
I want to get these cats
out of the rain.
[Music]
And then what?
Okay, sounds good.
Thank you so much.
Great news.
The shelter
has a foster program.
They said they can pick up
the cats tomorrow.
Thank goodness.
Whew. Glad to hear it!
How are you little guys
holding up?
Anyone need to use
the bathroom?
Make a phone call?
[Laughs]
You guys are gonna be just fine.
- I think I get it.
- Hm?
Why my future vision
has been so off.
I have to change the way
I think about you.
What?
I've been looking
into probable futures
where you act
like a child.
I keep expecting you
to run from responsibility
and to turn to me for help,
but you don't do that
anymore.
Those futures
aren't probable at all.
There's nothing wrong
with this timeline or
my future vision.
I just need to factor in
that you've grown up.
[Laughs]
I guess I have,
but it's only because I'm trying
to be more like you.
You always know
what to do.
Not always.
Okay, most of the time.
I want to adopt this one.
There's something about her.
- Really? Is that a probable future?
- It is now.
Besides, I've missed having
someone cute and vulnerable
to take care of.
I think I'll call her "Steven."
Isn't that gonna get confusing?
All right, then.
Cat Steven.
Oh, my gosh! Wow!
O-Oh, okay.
This is the best!
What, you're adopting one?
Too bad I couldn't get her
in your portrait,
which I managed to finish,
by the way.
[Gasps] Really?
What about our essence?
Well, I fudged it,
but I think I got it.
[Both gasp]
[Waves crashing]
[Kitten purring]
[Music]
- - Addic7ed.com - -