- - Addic7ed.com - -
[Explosions echo in distance]
[Ship whooshes, alarms blaring]
[Grunting]
Aaghh!
That did it!
Emerald is on the run!
Lars! We're hit!
Nothing's working!
Wha? Hold on...
Wh-what is your course?
We'll try and intercept ...
[Computer warbles]
Lars?!
What is wrong with you, ship?!
[Beeping]
Oh.
Pretty much everything.
Well... at least
the display works!
[Electricity crackles]
Aah!
[Screams]
[Music]
I can't pull up!
We're gonna crash!
Aaaaagh!
[Boom!]
[Heavy thudding]
[Gasps]
[Sighs] Oh, boy.
Where are we now?
Uh... hello?
A-Anybody out there?
Anyone at all?
[Yelps]
[Gasps]
Okay. We're fine.
I'm fine.
I'll find the ship's radio
and Lars'll pick us right up.
Whoa.
[Music]
[Computerized whirring]
The cockpit! [Exhales]
Hello?
This is Star Skipper
calling Sun Incinerator!
It's Stevonnie!
Steven and Connie?
We're stranded!
We need help!
Come on!
Don't leave me here!
[Radio crackles, whirring fades]
What do we do now?
That was our best chance...
We can't fix the radio.
The ship's beyond hope...
no one knows where we are!
[Groans]
What do we do?!
[Creature shrieks]
[Leaves rustle]
[Creature roars]
[Grunts]
[Growls, shrieks]
An alien!
[Shrieks]
Aah!
[Gasps]
[Music]
[Shrieks]
[Leaves rustle]
Uh, glad they're okay!
Wait.
If life can thrive here ...
then so can I.
I've just gotta hold out
till Lars finds me.
Until then...
we survive.
[Grunting]
[Music]
[Chomp!] Mmm.
[Inhales deeply]
[Bubbles gurgling]
[Laughs]
[Straining]
[Lightning crashes]
[Music]
[Laughs softly]
Come on. We have to!
We're out of energy bars!
But it's so cute!
But we need the protein
for a healthy diet!
There has to be
a better way!
We can just stick to fruit ...
fruit's good!
[Roars]
Aah!
[Panting]
[Music]
[Roars]
[Grunts]
[Beak snapping]
[Snorts]
Phew...
Huh...
Have I...
been here before?
No, that's ridiculous.
[Roaring in the distance]
Well, guess
I'm camping here tonight.
[Fire crackling]
Finally.
Goodnight, Stevonnie!
Goodnight, Stevonnie.
Sweet... dreams...
[Snoring]
Mm.
Hmm?
What?!
I-I'm... home?
Dr. Maheswaran: [Muffled] You were
told to be prepared cycles ago.
[Rumbling]
[Normally] There'll be no more
excuses. Get it done.
And don't expect me to look
kindly upon this transgression.
Embark at once.
Mom?
What is she talkin' about?
Huh?!
[Grunts]
Yes, I know there's organic life
on the surface.
It's an invasion.
Hey, mom!
What are you talking about!?
You will stick to my orders,
and you will destroy them!
[Sighs]
I hate it when she ignores me.
No.
[Panting]
[Sighs]
Mm...
[Grunts]
- No. I will not repeat myself.
- Whoa!
[Grunting]
- Hm.
- That is simply unacceptable.
[Sing-songy] Mom!
Well, you'll have to remember,
won't you.
[Huffs]
[Grunting] The dullness
of this exchange tires me.
Just land the drop ships and do
your pathetic job for once,
or I'll shatter you
and your crew myself.
Hey, mom!!
What are you doing?!
[Music]
Honey, please...
give me a moment.
[Ship whirrs]
Huh?
[Shrieks excitedly]
Whoa, cool!
Stevonnie: Yelloooooow!
Hey, Yellow!
Oh, you're still here.
What are you doing?
I'm commanding the dropships
to colonize this planet.
I wanna command
a drop ship!
Well, when you have
your own colony,
you can command
whatever you want.
I want a colony!
[Chiming]
I want one now!
What's this?!
I'm contacting the leader
of the fleet.
Let me do it!
[Chiming]
Aah! Whoa!
Don't touch that!
[Huffs]
Why not?!
You have so many worlds
and I don't even have one!
It's not fair!
I. Want. One.
I want my own army!
I want my own planet!
I deserve it!
I'm just as important as you!
Then why don't you
act like it...
Pink?
[Music]
[Growls]
[Gasps]
Whoa!
[Panting]
Steven, what was that?
Diamonds...
I'm having Diamond dreams
again, but why now?
Why... here?
[Music]
No way...
[Grunts]
This is just like the moon base
orbiting Earth.
[Grunts]
Whoa, now...
That must have been
a colony...
Wait a second...
[Music]
Pink Diamond was here...
Oh!
[Panting]
And Yellow!
[Grunting]
That's it!
I hope this thing still works!
Hmm...
That pattern...
[Chiming]
[Beeping]
Nope.
Nuh-uh.
Ugh, yikes!
[Gasps]
It's Lars' ship!
Keep searching!
We're not giving up on them!
No matter what!
Lars! Hey, Lars!
Hey, Lars!
There you are! We've been
looking all over for you!
Oh, my gosh, Lars!
It's so good to see you.
Set a course for their signal!
It's good to see you, too.
[Sighs] Thanks, Lars...
[Thudding]
[Muffled roar]
Hello, bird blob, my old friend.
[Chuckles nervously]
[Roars]
[Glass cracking]
Lars, hurry!
We've got company!
[Ship whirring]
Yeehaw!
Ugh, what the heck is that?!
I don't know, but it's not
here to play nice!
Charge the blasters!
[Energy crackles]
[Music]
[Creature warbles]
[Exhales deeply]
[Ship whirs]
Ha!
Looks like
we just saved your butts!
Lets get you up here
and back home through my head.
Yeah, I think I'm ready to go home.
- - Addic7ed.com - -