- Garnet: # We #
- # Are the Crystal #
- Steven: # Gems #
- # we'll always save the day #
Steven: # and if you think we can't #
All: # we'll always find a way #
- # that's why the people #
- # of this world #
Garnet: # believe in... Garnet #
- # Amethyst #
- # and Pearl #
Steven: # And Steven! #
- - Addic7ed.com - -
- Steven, come on!
- Sorry.
I just had to make sure
I had everything.
I bet Lars will really
appreciate this package
his parents put together
for him.
And MC Bear Bear!
To hug if he gets scared.
I'm so excited
we're finally going to have
a space adventure
together.
Steven and Connie
in space!
I'm not so sure
this is gonna be an adventure.
Last time I saw Lars,
he was huddled up in a dark cave
with some other
Homeworld fugitives.
Oh. Yeah.
Well, I'm ready
for anything.
Lion. You ready?
[Groans]
- Eee!
- Oh, my gah.
- We have to stay on task.
- Mm.
[Grumbles]
[music]
- Aah!
- Waah!
- Steven.
- Lars?
It's over! I've got you now,
you miserable off colors!
You'll never take us alive,
Emerald!
W-What is going on?
Captain,
I'm having a vision.
We're about to be discovered...
by Emerald!
- W-Wait. Captain?!
Thanks, Padparadscha.
Fluorite,
how are the engines looking?
Le-e-t me-e-e
che-e-e-ck.
Twins, fire up
the nova thrusters.
- Yes, captain.
- Right away, captain.
No! No!
Those are my nova thrusters!
That is my ship!
Rhodonite,
everything clear up ahead?
For now.
It was a minor inconvenience
when you stole
my personal shuttle
and crashed it
on Upsilon 9.
It was an insult
when you impersonated
imperial officers
during a cosmic jubilee.
[Both laughing]
But to steal my Sun Incinerator
is unacceptable!
If this ship means
so much to you,
maybe you shouldn't
have left it unguarded
in the docking bay
of Klavius 7.
There were 67 elite Citrines
guarding it!
Oh. I didn't see them.
No, wait. I did.
They didn't see us.
Oh, I'll get you!
I'll get you myself!
I'll do it right now.
[Chuckling] I'll blow you up
to smithereens!
Good luck catching us.
We stole your fastest ship!
The engines are a-a-all se-e-t.
Twins, hyperspeed us
out of here.
- Right.
You will not go at hyperspeed!
- Bingo, bongo.
- Off colors!
Man, she's been on my tail
since sector four.
That's like three sectors ago.
Get over it, right?
Lars!
I have so many questions!
Uh, where'd you get
this ship?
And more importantly,
where'd you get that cape?
[Chuckles] Stole 'em.
Ste-e-e-ven.
Is tha-a-t...another...
human frie-e-nd?
Yeah, I'm Connie.
Happy to be aboard.
You must all be Lars' crew.
[Chuckles]
They're more than that.
Without them, I'd still be stuck
in a cave on the Gem Homeworld.
They were able to figure out
a way off that lame old planet.
But we never would have been
able to steal a ship without Lars.
He can slip past
all the scanners undetected.
Her name is Connie.
And now a few stolen ships and
a couple of space crimes later,
we're finally on a course
toward Earth.
Hey, you know,
speaking of Earth,
your parents
put this together for you.
Oh!
Oh, finally! Clean jeans!
Oh, man!
And my skull gauges!
These are perfect!
[Sighs] They'd didn't
have to do all this.
I'll be back on Earth soon.
We are excited
about your Beach City.
I look forward to a planet
of sand and water.
Yeah! And my house.
And my trampoline.
The Big Donut!
And Sadie.
How is Sadie?
Oh, really,
really good!
Oh. Yeah?
Now she's Sadie Killer
and the Suspects.
Her band is awesome.
She looks really happy...
...without me.
[Alarm blaring]
What's going on?
Lars? Lars! Lars!
Captain Lars, a huge battleship
is approaching fast.
It'll be here
in just five quads.
What are your orders?
I don't believe this.
[Inhales] How is she having
such a good time without me?!
Does she even know
I died out here?!
Of course she does!
She's been worried sick!
Already three quads away.
What should we do?
We could drop out of warp
and ambush them,
but that might be
too risky.
Or maybe we find a nearby planet
to hide on?
I'm not sure!
What do you usually do?
Usually?
Usually we just follow
Captain Lars' orders!
Captain Lars has taken
so many risks on our behalf.
We need him!
Oh, no!
The warning alarm!
We're in danger!
Do you hear that?
Your crew needs you.
You don't get it,
do you, Steven?
[Sniffles]
It should be me.
[Crying] I'm the one
that should be hanging out
with the cool kids!
She's getting back at me
for everything I've done!
Do you really think
Sadie is living her life
just to get back at you?
Why else would she be having
so much fun without me?!
Because life goes on,
no matter what happens.
She was so upset
when she found out
you'd be stuck in space,
Lars.
She really misses you,
but she can't stay sad forever.
She started hanging out
with the cool kids.
She quit the Big Donut
all because she needed to do
something to feel better.
And look at you!
Steven said you'd be hiding
in some cave on Homeworld,
but you're not.
You're out here
fighting for freedom
with all your new friends
in tow!
Are you doing any of this
to hurt Sadie?
No! I'm doing this
because I have to.
I'd never do this
to hurt Sadie because ...
- Because!
- Because you're best friends!
And best friends wouldn't do
anything to hurt each other.
Whoa.
It's here. An imperial warship
has just caught up to us.
- What?
- An imperial warship?
The Destiny Destroyer!
Their main weapons
are pointed right at us!
Hmm, pulling out
the big guns just for us, huh?
With a ship like that,
Emerald could wipe us out
in an instant,
if she really wanted to.
Of course she wants to!
Incoming message
from the Destiny Destroyer.
Onscreen.
[Laughs]
Did you really think
I wasn't going to be able
to track my own ship?
The Sun Incinerator's
specialized nova thrusters
give off an energy signature
I could recognize
from the other side
of the galaxy.
Now surrender to me
or be destroyed!
[Laughs]
I'd never surrender to you!
Blow us into stardust
like you've always dreamed of.
Very well.
Prepare yourselves
for destruction!
Lars,
what are you doing?!
Drop the shields,
Rhodonite.
But that would leave us open
to their attack!
We wouldn't stand
a chance!
Trust me,
we'll be just fine.
- Now lower the shields.
- But...
The destroyer's weapons
are charged at 90%.
They're preparing
to open fire!
Lower the shields!
That's an order!
[Gulps]
L-Lowering shields.
[All screaming]
Twins, what's our status?
Our weapons and shields have
been knocked offline, but...
Otherwise, we're fine.
We're still...alive!
The lasers
barely grazed us!
Emerald is about to attack,
but she's going to miss
on purpose.
[Chuckles]
Bingo, bongo!
What do you think
you're doing?!
[Laughing]
You really do have a heart,
don't you, Emerald?
W-What?!
You're not going to hurt
this ship!
You love this ship!
it's your best friend.
You'd much rather
let it get away than destroy it.
[Giggles]
Wow, Lars, I missed you.
You're right about that.
I won't destroy
my beautiful ship.
But I will make it
so you can't get away!
Aim for their nova thrusters!
[All shouting]
Evasive maneuvers!
If only our weapons and shields
were online.
I think she has us
this time.
Unless we use that.
That?!
No-o-o-t tha-a-a-a-t.
- What's that?
- The captain's experimental fighter jet
that only he knows how to drive.
It's too risky!
We're out of options.
But, Lars, your crew needs you
here on the ship.
You got a better idea?
Captain Lars,
permission to go in your place.
If it's anything like
driving a car, I should be fine.
Permission...granted!
Take out the enemy's
main cannons
while we get our weapons system
and shields back online.
Fluorite, how long
before we have full power
to shields and weapons?
Give me fi-i-ve minu-u-tes.
Can they really fly it?
If anyone can fly it, I'm sure
it's friends of our captain.
[Grunts] Whoa!
It is like a car!
We'll watch your back while you
take out those guns. Now launch!
Captain Lars is about to give
the order to launch.
Okay. Launching.
Get in close!
They can't aim at themselves.
Roger.
Target within range.
Targeting!
One down! That's two!
Yes! All right!
Everything's almost fixed here.
Come on back.
Incoming missiles straight ahead!
It's too late, Lars.
I can't...
[Screams]
Steven?! Connie?!
Nooooo!
- - Addic7ed.com - -