- Garnet: # We #
- # Are the Crystal #
- Steven: # Gems #
- # we'll always save the day #
Steven: # and if you think we can't #
All: # we'll always find a way #
- # that's why the people #
- # of this world #
Garnet: # believe in...
Garnet #
- # Amethyst #
- # and Pearl #
Steven: # And Steven! #
~ Addic7ed.com ~
Aquamarine: The Rose Quartz.
Can you believe it?
And she just handed herself in.
That's right.
You caught me.
Galactic Criminal Rose Quartz.
I love shattering Diamonds.
I just want to shatter 'em
all the time.
You think shattering's bad?
Wait till the Diamonds
get their hands on you.
At least everyone else is safe.
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
[Grunting]
- Steven!
- What the... Lars!
Oh! Looks like we got
one of the humans anyway.
Don't know what we'll do
with just one of them,
but I guess that's
for the Diamonds to decide.
Wait.
Aquamarine, the deal is off.
You were only supposed
to take me. No humans.
That's a human.
[Grunting]
Oh, no.
Is Rosie upset 'cause her widdle
"deal" didn't work?
Look.
I'm so moved, I'm crying.
[Laughs]
Just kidding.
That's my gem.
Topaz, what do you think?
Should we let her friend go?
I agree.
[Laughs]
Go on. Do your thing.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Not again.
I'll go let the Diamonds know
about our little prisoner.
Say, Rose, how do I look?
Awful, small, and mean!
[Laughs]
Is that how you flattered
so many Gems
into joining
your rebellion?
How cute.
Topaz, I trust you'll still be
able to fly the ship
despite your...
you know.... additions?
[Laughs]
Lars: Steven,
this is all your fault.
All this weird alien stuff ...
this is 'cause of you, isn't it?
Yes, of course it is!
That's why I turned myself in ...
to save all of you!
Well, it didn't really work out
too well, did it?
Well, everyone else managed
to get off the ship.
So, where were you?
I ran and hid, Steven,
like any sensible person
would... do
if they wanted to get trapped
on a ship.
Oh.
Lars.
Sadie was in trouble,
and I didn't do anything.
Actually, wait.
I did do something.
I ran and hid
just like I always do.
Just like I ran
from the potluck.
But you were abducted.
That's not your fault.
No, I trashed my roll
and ran away.
Then I was abducted.
Oh, why couldn't I just let
people eat my food?!
[Sighs]
We have to get you
out of here.
Here,
just leave it to me.
Hey! Look!
You have Rose Quartz!
Why bother with him?
He's worthless!
Thanks a lot, Steven.
No! I meant like "worth less",
not "worthless"
like... relative to me.
[Sighs]
At least I make
a great seat cushion.
You feeling cozy,
you big banana?
I don't think
she's listening.
Can you hear me, you ...
What was it Jamie said?
You dangerous yellow coat?
Of course
she can't hear you, Steven.
She's got
those big headphones on.
[Sighs]
[Rumbling]
[Grunting]
[Sighs]
Those Crystal Gems must have
screwed up the engine
during takeoff.
Topaz, go fix it.
Lars, look for something
that can help us.
[Grunts]
[Beeps]
[Gasps]
A destabilizer.
That's perfect!
A destaba-what?
It's a weapon that disrupts
a Gem's physical form.
Cool.
Thanks for explaining.
I still don't know
what that means.
Just hear me out.
I have a plan.
I'm gonna need you
to be my arms.
Ugh. Fine.
Lars, pull my pants off.
What?!
Trust me!
I'm trying to save you.
What if I don't want
to be saved?
What if I want to stay trapped
here and fly around space,
and why your pants,
you weirdo?!
Just do it!
[Pants unzip]
Ugh.
There. I did it.
Great. Now tie one of the legs
into a lasso.
I can't.
They're on the floor.
What are they doing
on the floor?!
I don't know, Steven.
What are we doing in space?
Lars, pick them up
and then tie them into a lasso.
Ugh. Fine.
Wow. It worked.
We're back home.
Great plan.
[Sighs]
Now lasso
the destabilizer.
I still don't know
what that is.
That.
That thing.
Come on, Lars.
You can do it.
Ugh. Fine.
[Grunts weakly]
Come on.
Just one more try.
I don't want to try again.
Lars, throw the lasso!
Fine!
What is your problem,
Lars?!
Why did you do that?!
Why do you think I'm capable
of anything?!
You think I can do
all this stuff, but I can't!
I can't because...
I'm a wuss, Steven.
I'm just [sniffles] afraid.
I've always just been stupid
and afraid.
Not like you.
You're always helping people.
You're never afraid.
[Sniffles]
Lars...
I'm afraid right now.
I thought if I turned myself in,
it'd fix everything, but...
I don't want to do this,
Lars.
I've been to space before,
but not like this.
They're taking me straight
to their terrible leaders
that want to destroy Earth
and destroy me
for something
I never even did.
I just wanted to save everyone,
but I couldn't even do that
because, look ...
you're still here.
Steven.
I'm sorry.
I don't know how I'm gonna
get you out of this.
We'll figure it out.
We've got like
a billion light-years
till we get there,
right?
For the first time ever,
you're gonna look
on the bright side?
Y-You don't have
to sugarcoat this,
but come on,
you never do that.
You're always real with me about
how much everything sucks.
Okay. You're right.
This is really, really
messed up, Steven.
You know what's even more
messed up?
Even though
you're in huge trouble
and it's all my fault...
I'm kind of glad
you're here.
I...
I don't want to be alone
right now.
[Sobs]
Isn't that awful?
Dude, at this point,
everything is awful.
[Chuckles]
[Both chuckle]
I'd give you a hug,
but I can't use my arms.
I could try using my legs,
but it might be weird.
[Crying]
That's so, so beautiful.
[Sniffles]
Even in the clutches
of certain doom,
you're happy
to have each other.
[Gasps]
T-T-Topaz.
I don't know what Topaz would do
if she didn't have Topaz.
I've always wanted
to tell me
how I'm helping me
through this,
but there's always someone
between us!
They're always sending me
on these miserable missions.
I'm always pretending
I'm fine with it.
[Sniffles]
I have to pretend I'm fine.
But you two ...
you're so honest and open...
so [sniffles]
I want to help you guys.
What do you need?
A way off this ship.
And my pants.
All right.
You can use this escape pod.
I'll set the coordinates
for Earth.
All right, Lars, just get in
and let it do its thing.
Guh. What are you talking about?
You're coming, right?
I can't.
I turned myself in.
I still got to go.
Someone's got to pay
for what my mom did.
But you don't want to do this?
Dude, forget it.
Let's just go.
- I ...
- Aquamarine: Topaz, what are you
still doing down here,
you big boulder?
We're almost to Homeworld.
[Gasps]
What... are... you... doing?
Look, I can explain.
Um, they had this whole
heartfelt thing
about being there for each
other, and you missed it.
It was so moving.
[Gasps] No! Wait!
I can't see what's happening.
Are we still escaping?
No!
Nobody's escaping!
Aquamarine,
let's talk about this.
Yeah, I-I bet you don't
really want to hurt us.
You ... You probably
just act mean
because deep down
you're afraid you're weak.
Go ahead. Let it out.
We're all sharing right now.
Topaz, you had one job,
and if you're not
gonna do it,
you're of no use to me!
[Whimpers]
Ooh!
So... a revolt, huh?
And what do you plan to do
after this?
Go back to the Diamonds?
My gem in your hand?
I'm sure
they'll love that.
You'll be rewarded
handsomely
by being separated
and shattered.
[Clatters]
[Thuds]
What was I thinking?
That's the problem
with you fusions.
Sooner or later,
you all become sentimental.
[Rumbles]
We're here.
Look, just unfuse,
and we'll never speak of this
again.
[Steven and Lars grunting]
Topaz, you don't have to do this.
[Grunting continues]
Wait. Lars!
- Steven, where are they taking us?!
- I don't know!
- Steven!
- Lars!
~ Addic7ed.com ~