- Garnet: # We #
- # Are the Crystal #
- Steven: # Gems #
- # we'll always save the day #
Steven: # and if you think we can't #
All: # we'll always find a way #
- # that's why the people #
- # of this world #
Garnet: # believe in...
Garnet #
- # Amethyst #
- # and Pearl #
Steven: # And Steven! #
sync & corr. by f1nc0
- Addic7ed.com -
[Seagulls squawking]
[Door chimes]
Thanks for coming.
- Hey, Sadie!
- Hey, Steven. What'll it be?
Sorry to be a pain,
but I got kind of a long order.
I hope it's not
too much trouble.
What trouble?
[Chuckles]
I'm a professional
doughnut girl.
Okay...
I'll have one jelly doughnut
with powdered sugar on the side,
three chocolate frosted,
one frosted chocolate,
two chocolate-frosted
chocolate,
one dog-nut ...
medium well ...
one coffee with milk and sugar,
hold the coffee.
I also have
several methods of payment
I'd like you to split
this order across evenly.
- Uh, what's all this for?
- Band practice.
- You're in a band?!
- Kinda.
I started jamming with Jenny,
Buck, and Sour Cream!
Whoa!
That's so cool!
Aw, man!
I bet you guys sound amazing!
We're still trying
to figure out our sound,
but it's been fun just
playing music with other people.
It's also nice to have an outlet
that doesn't involve space and gem stuff
and everything else going on.
Um...
You doing okay?
Well, I worry about Lars
being in space,
and I hope he's safe
and all but... [Sighs]
Working all these shifts
by myself has been a huge drag.
I'm totally used to doing his work,
but I'm used to at least
having him here to talk to.
Now I got to do that myself, too.
Oh, come on, Sadie,
you missed a spot!
Oh, no, sorry.
Well, we'll all be practicing
at Sour Cream's place tonight.
- Feel free to stop by if you have time.
- I'll try!
Hopefully I can finish
restocking napkins early.
We're always running out,
for some reason.
Hmm, weird.
Well, see ya, Sadie!
Bye, Steven.
[Electronic beats playing]
What do ya call that style?
- Beach core.
- Buck: Hey.
- What's up, Buck?
- Guess who's got a gig
at Delmarva's number-two music
and seafood festival this weekend?!
Chuji and the Woo Woos?
- Jack and the Frosted Tips?
- 7-Force?
No, us!
All: What?!
- We don't even have a name yet!
- Or a set list!
Or even one single song
to put on a set list!
[Sighs]
Guess we got a lot of work to do.
What if we went for
a more of a rap-a-billy style?
- No, thanks.
- How about something like...
♪ Here we are ♪
♪ Our hearts combining ♪
♪ Music and friends,
our souls aligning ♪
Buck: Hold on, Steven.
You got a really cool sentiment
going on
that can resonate
with a wide audience.
I just feel like
this seafood festival
needs to hear something
challenging and provocative.
Check this out.
[Guitar strumming]
♪ Doo-doo ♪
♪ Butt ♪
♪ The government ♪
- # Corrupts #
- Jenny: Hold on there, Bucky D.
I'm all for being socially conscious
and waking people up inside,
but people are gonna be at
this seafood fest to have fun!
Let's give them something
they can dance to!
- Sour Cream, give me a beat!
- A what?
A beat!
[Echoing] # Beat #
Oh, yeah!
Let's spice it up!
[Funky riff plays]
Cool!
Yeah!
And then how about some...
[Screeching tones play]
- What the heck, Sour Cream?!
- What?
Can't let your audience
get too comfortable.
Maybe we should just call it
a night and try again tomorrow.
- Agreed.
- Sadie: Oh, hey, guys!
Sorry I'm so late.
Took longer to close up
than I thought it would.
- Y'all still practicing?
- Oh, sorry, Sadie, we just wrapped up.
- We were getting nowhere.
- Aw, shoot!
I really wanted to hear you guys.
Well, let me know if you
have another band practice
when I'm not working.
- See ya, guys.
- Bye, Sadie!
- Later.
- Bye, Sadie.
See ya, girl.
[Dog barking in distance]
[Sprinkler whirring]
- Steven: Hi, Sadie!
- S'up?
- Hey, how's it goin'?
- Hey, girl.
Whoa! Hey, guys!
I just got home from work.
[Chuckles]
We know. We followed you.
Sorry if that's weird.
We know how busy
your schedule is,
so we decided
to bring the jam to you.
Aw, shucks, guys!
But...
[Groans nervously]
My room
is such a mess right now.
Okay, ah, okay, just give me
a moment to tidy up!
Dang, Sadie! You've got
so much space in here!
Yo, Sadie, do you have
any free outlets to plug into?
- Oh, yeah, check over by the TV.
- Let's get serious now.
- The show is this weekend!
- Wait...
I can't really feel the music
in this cramped spot.
- This looks comfy.
- No, wait!
[Crunch] Aw, doo-doo.
I think I broke your bed.
[Grunts]
Sour Cream: Whoa!
Scary movies!
Hey, Sadie,
you've got a dark side.
It's more of a dork side.
Jenny: Hey, is that "The Lurch"?
- You know this one?
- Yeah! It's a classic!
I can't believe you have a copy!
Guys, we have to watch this.
Brains!
[Groaning]
[Screams]
I can't believe you like this one.
Not everyone appreciates
Bulgarian horror.
Uh, guys, don't we need
to find our sound?
I kind of like this sound.
[Eerie music playing]
[Dark electronic beat plays]
Ooh. I like that.
[Bass playing]
And then, we can do this.
[Guitar strumming]
Now we just need
some provocative lyrics.
♪ Tired ♪
- # From work #
- Nice.
[Chuckles]
♪ Hate ♪
♪ My job ♪
[Guitar playing]
♪ I really oughta be in mourning ♪
♪ But I've got another shift
this morning ♪
♪ Everyday feels like
it's never-ending ♪
♪ What's the point of all
this time I'm spending ♪
♪ Here ♪
♪ At this ♪
♪ Dead-end job ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ We are the working dead ♪
♪ And we lurch
for minimum wage ♪
♪ But I'd really rather be ♪
♪ Eating your brain ♪
♪ Look at you ...
you seem so bright and healthy ♪
♪ And your minds are
full of joy and wonder ♪
♪ Stay a thousand miles
from the condition ♪
♪ That I've got
from all the stress I'm under ♪
♪ Don't come near me
or you might encourage ♪
♪ All these terrifying sudden urges ♪
♪ Seeing you makes
skipping work so tempting ♪
♪ Don't you know
that in the night, I'm temping ♪
♪ Here ♪
♪ At this ♪
♪ Dead-end job ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ We are the working dead ♪
♪ And we lurch for minimum wage ♪
♪ But I'd really rather be ♪
♪ Eating your brain ♪
[Woman screaming]
- Whoa!
- Sadie, that was awesome!
- Yeah, girl, yeah!
That was so rad!
You're not Sadie Miller,
you're Sadie Killer.
This is it!
This is our sound!
Sadie, you should be our frontman!
Really?!
[Chuckling] Wow, I...
Uh, wait, no, I can't.
Ugh, I've got to work tomorrow.
Actually, you guys
should probably pack up.
I got to get some rest
before my shift.
Aw, doo-doo.
[Seagulls squawking]
[Door chimes]
Hey.
What're you doing here?
I was just wondering
if I could get some advice.
We've been trying to write
some more spooky songs
without you, but...
they sound so phony
coming from me.
Rawr, I'm a bad, bad boy!
Yeesh. I don't know.
I can't do it like you.
You got any tips?
Let's see.
First, lose your youth
to your boring job.
Then lose the only person
you've ever felt truly close to.
And then lose your mind
working all his shifts.
I don't think I can do all that
before the show tomorrow.
[Chuckles nervously]
Are you sure you can't come?
I'm the only employee at
the shop. I can't just leave.
Singing is fun,
and being in the band
would be really fun ...
like the most fun ever.
B-But a lot of things
could be a lot of things.
This job is a drag,
but at last I know it's a drag.
It's normal.
There's something nice
about that, you know?
Hanging out,
singing and stuff,
it feels so not normal.
It's like ...
you ever feel so bad
that you feel good?
Like when you get so cold
that it burns.
Sometimes I just want
to scream my guts out.
Well, no not my guts,
but whatever thing is
squirming around in my guts.
Wow!
That ... That's poetry!
You're such a natural at this.
All right, I'll try my best.
How's this?
♪ Hate my job,
hate my job ♪
♪ Obligations ♪
♪ No vacations ♪
♪ Kinda sa-a-a-d ♪
Do I really sound like that?
No, no, y-you sing it like
it's really a problem for you.
Don't worry, I'll get it,
I promise.
♪ Squirming in my guts ♪
♪ I got to sell doughnuts ♪
♪ Big doughnut... ♪
[Humming]
[Insects chirping]
I can't believe your car
can hold all these amps.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, it's Steven Universe.
Is that the scariest jacket
you could find?
Mm-hmm. Hope it doesn't
scare anyone too much.
- So... no Sadie Killer, huh?
- 'Fraid not. She's just...
- too busy with work.
- Aw, man!
This gig won't be the same
without her.
All right, Steven,
you're gonna have to
up your scary game
to fill Sadie's shoes.
Got it!
Rawr!
You can't help being cute,
no more than I can help
being cool. Let's go.
[Engine starts]
Okay.
Jenny: Buckle up, y'all.
Hope the seafood
at this thing is good.
So where is this place exactly?
Buck: I gave you the directions.
Oh, that tiny piece of paper?
Where'd I put it?
- Did it fall under the seat?
- I don't see it back here.
Yo, what if this...
was all a dream?
- [Groans] This is not ...
- Sadie: Hey! Wait up!
[Panting]
- Sadie!
I can do it!
I can do the show!
I can come!
- All right! Yeah!
- Oh, thank goodness!
And I can come to practice,
and I can come to the next show
and the show after that!
But, Sadie,
don't you have work?
Ha! I quit!
sync & corr. by f1nc0
- Addic7ed.com -